<?xml version="1.0"?>
<LEWIS>
    <REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="5544" NEWID="1">
<DATE>26-FEB-1987 15:01:01.79</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>cocoa</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>el-salvador</D><D>usa</D><D>uruguay</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
C T
f0704reute
u f BC-BAHIA-COCOA-REVIEW   02-26 0105</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT>
<TITLE>BAHIA COCOA REVIEW</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    SALVADOR, Feb 26 - </DATELINE><BODY>Showers continued throughout the week in
the Bahia cocoa zone, alleviating the drought since early
January and improving prospects for the coming temporao,
although normal humidity levels have not been restored,
Comissaria Smith said in its weekly review.
    The dry period means the temporao will be late this year.
    Arrivals for the week ended February 22 were 155,221 bags
of 60 kilos making a cumulative total for the season of 5.93
mln against 5.81 at the same stage last year. Again it seems
that cocoa delivered earlier on consignment was included in the
arrivals figures.
    Comissaria Smith said there is still some doubt as to how
much old crop cocoa is still available as harvesting has
practically come to an end. With total Bahia crop estimates
around 6.4 mln bags and sales standing at almost 6.2 mln there
are a few hundred thousand bags still in the hands of farmers,
middlemen, exporters and processors.
    There are doubts as to how much of this cocoa would be fit
for export as shippers are now experiencing dificulties in
obtaining +Bahia superior+ certificates.
    In view of the lower quality over recent weeks farmers have
sold a good part of their cocoa held on consignment.
    Comissaria Smith said spot bean prices rose to 340 to 350
cruzados per arroba of 15 kilos.
    Bean shippers were reluctant to offer nearby shipment and
only limited sales were booked for March shipment at 1,750 to
1,780 dlrs per tonne to ports to be named.
    New crop sales were also light and all to open ports with
June/July going at 1,850 and 1,880 dlrs and at 35 and 45 dlrs
under New York july, Aug/Sept at 1,870, 1,875 and 1,880 dlrs
per tonne FOB.
    Routine sales of butter were made. March/April sold at
4,340, 4,345 and 4,350 dlrs.
    April/May butter went at 2.27 times New York May, June/July
at 4,400 and 4,415 dlrs, Aug/Sept at 4,351 to 4,450 dlrs and at
2.27 and 2.28 times New York Sept and Oct/Dec at 4,480 dlrs and
2.27 times New York Dec, Comissaria Smith said.
    Destinations were the U.S., Covertible currency areas,
Uruguay and open ports.
    Cake sales were registered at 785 to 995 dlrs for
March/April, 785 dlrs for May, 753 dlrs for Aug and 0.39 times
New York Dec for Oct/Dec.
    Buyers were the U.S., Argentina, Uruguay and convertible
currency areas.
    Liquor sales were limited with March/April selling at 2,325
and 2,380 dlrs, June/July at 2,375 dlrs and at 1.25 times New
York July, Aug/Sept at 2,400 dlrs and at 1.25 times New York
Sept and Oct/Dec at 1.25 times New York Dec, Comissaria Smith
said.
    Total Bahia sales are currently estimated at 6.13 mln bags
against the 1986/87 crop and 1.06 mln bags against the 1987/88
crop.
    Final figures for the period to February 28 are expected to
be published by the Brazilian Cocoa Trade Commission after
carnival which ends midday on February 27.
 Reuter
</BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="NO" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="5715" NEWID="172">
<DATE>26-FEB-1987 17:50:20.87</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   A
   f0247 reute
r f BC-U.S.-REGULATOR-CLOSES   02-26 0102</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>U.S. REGULATOR CLOSES BANKS IN TEXAS, LOUISIANA</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    WASHINGTON, Feb 26 - </DATELINE><BODY>The Federal Deposit Insurance Corp
(FDIC) said three troubled banks in Texas and Louisiana were
merged with healthy financial institutions.
    The FDIC said it subsidized the merger of Central Bank and
Trust Co, Glenmora, La., with the healthy Peoples Bank and
Trust Co, Natchitoches, La., after state regulators notified it
that Central was in danger of failing.
    Central had assets of 28.3 mln dlrs.
    The FDIC said the deposits of the failed Farmers State
Bank, Hart, Tex., were assumed by Hale County State Bank,
Plainview, Tex.
    Farmers, with 9.6 mln dlrs in assets, was closed by Texas
bank regulators.
    The deposits of the failed First National Bank of Crosby,
Crosby, Tex., with total assets of 8.2 mln dlrs, were assumed
by Central Bancshares of the South Inc, Birmingham, Ala., after
First National was closed by federal bank regulators, the FDIC
said.
    The number of federally insured banks to fail so far this
year now totals 32, the FDIC said.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="NO" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="18311" NEWID="1893">
<DATE> 4-MAR-1987 20:56:47.86</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>new-zealand</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   RM
   f0136 reute
u f BC-N.Z.-WRITES-OFF-MEAT   03-04 0114</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>N.Z. WRITES OFF MEAT PRICE STABILISATION DEBT</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    WELLINGTON, March 5 - </DATELINE><BODY>New Zealand agreed with the Meat
Producers Board to write off 1.03 billion N.Z. Dlrs of debt
incurred on behalf of farmers under the Meat Price
Stabilisation Scheme, Finance Minister Roger Douglas said.
    Douglas and Agriculture Minister Colin Moyle said in a
joint statement the agreement concludes one of the major
refinancing arrangements announced in the July 1986 budget,
which removed subsidies from the farming sector.
    The write-off applies to debt occurring prior to October
1985, when stabilisation payments for sheepmeat ceased under an
industry restructuring which allowed private marketing.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="18848" NEWID="2430">
<DATE> 5-MAR-1987 16:07:27.88</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>france</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   A RM
   f0732 reute
r f AM-TUNNEL   03-05 0113</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>EUROTUNNEL TO OFFER CHOICE OF INVESTMENTS</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    PARIS, March 5 - </DATELINE><BODY>Eurotunnel, the Anglo-French channel
tunnel consortium, will offer potential backers a wide choice
of ways to invest in a planned 750 mln stg capital issue later
this year, co-Chairman Alastair Morton said.
    Speaking to reporters after a shareholders meeting, he said
Eurotunnel would offer "a menu of securities" designed to
overcome investor reluctance.
    Details are still to be worked out but investors could be
offered a choice of paying immediately for shares or buying
them on a part-paid basis, or buying convertible bonds, or
bonds with warrants giving a right to buy shares at a later
date, he said.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="18854" NEWID="2436">
<DATE> 5-MAR-1987 16:12:38.07</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>grain</D><D>corn</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>brazil</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   C G
   f0749 reute
u f BC-MAIZE-IMPORTS-SUSPEND   03-05 0121</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>BRAZIL SUSPENDS IMPORT OF 500,000 TONNES MAIZE</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    SAO PAULO, March 5 - </DATELINE><BODY>Brazil has suspended the importation
of 500,000 tonnes of maize ordered last year because of the
excellent domestic maize harvest expected this year,
Agriculture Minister Iris Resende said.
    The Agriculture Ministry expects a record maize crop of
27.7 mln tonnes, a 36 pct increase on last year's crop of 20.3
mln tonnes. 
    Brazil's total grain crop is expected to be 65.3 mln
tonnes. "This is a record in the history of Brazilian
agriculture," a ministry spokesman said.
    Resende announced suspension of the maize imports at a news
conference in Brasilia yesterday.
    The ministry spokesman said he had no other details on the
maize transaction.
 Reuter London
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="19446" NEWID="3028">
<DATE> 9-MAR-1987 09:01:34.94</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>ship</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>brazil</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   C G L M T
   f0951 reute
u f BC-BRAZIL-SEAMEN-CONTINU   03-09 0114</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>BRAZIL SEAMEN CONTINUE STRIKE DESPITE COURT</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    RIO DE JANEIRO, March 9 - </DATELINE><BODY>Hundreds of marines were on alert
at 11 key Brazilian ports after 40,000 seamen decided to remain
on indefinite strike, even after the Higher Labour Court
Saturday ruled it illegal, union leaders said.
    The halt, the first national strike by seamen in 25 years,
started on February 27, and union leaders said they would not
return to work unless they got a 275 pct pay rise. Shipowners
have offered a 100 per cent raise, which the seamen rejected.
    "We have nothing to lose. If they want to lay off the
workers, fine, but we are determined to carry on with our
protest until the end," a union leader said.
 more
    He said they had decided in a meeting that if the marines
take over the ships, the seamen would abandon the vessels and
let the marines handle the situation by themselves.
    A spokesman for the Rio de Janeiro Port said the order to
send marines to take over the ports was given by Navy Minister
Henrique Saboya on grounds that ports are areas of national
security. But he said there were no incidents. The strike has
cut exports and imports and made an estimated 160 ships idle.
    Petrol station owners in four states also continued their
shutdown and there were fears that the combination of the two
stoppages could lead to a serious fuel shortage.
 Reuter London
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="NO" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="19447" NEWID="3029">
<DATE> 9-MAR-1987 09:06:39.94</DATE>
<TOPICS>London</TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F A
   f0971 reute
r f BC-BANKING-TRADE-GROUP-S   03-09 0098</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>BANKING TRADE GROUP SAYS BANK PROFITS DOWN</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    WASHINGTON, March 9 - </DATELINE><BODY>The American Bankers Association said
the profitability of the nation's commercial banks declined by
12 pct during the first three quarters of 1986.
    During the first nine months of last year, the industry's
annualized rate of return on assets dropped to 0.68 pct from
0.77 pct in the same period in 1985, the ABA said. Return on
equity fell to 10.8 pct from 12.3 pct the previous year.
    Despite the decline in profits, the ABA said banks' capital
grew boosting the industry's capital ratio to 6.4 pct from 6.3
pct.
    The number and size of banks losing money during the period
increased significantly, the ABA said.
    During the first nine months of 1986, 17.5 pct of banks,
holding 9.6 pct of banking assets, were unprofitable, the group
said. That compares with 13 pct of banks, holding 8.8 pct of
assets, during the same period in 1985, it said.
    The industry's provisions for loan losses increased to 0.73
pct of assets during the period, up from 0.59 pct of assets
during the same period in 1985, the group said.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="19449" NEWID="3031">
<DATE> 9-MAR-1987 09:11:10.46</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>money-fx</D><D>gnp</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>belgium</D><D>west-germany</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS><D>ec</D></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   RM
   f0984 reute
r f BC-BONN-SERIOUS-ABOUT-CU   03-09 0090</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>BONN SERIOUS ABOUT CURRENCY PACT, SAYS TIETMEYER</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    BRUSSELS, March 9 - </DATELINE><BODY>West Germany takes "very seriously" the
recent undertaking by major industrial countries to promote
exchange rate stability around current levels, Finance Ministry
State Secretary Hans Tietmeyer said.
    Talking to journalists before a meeting of European
Community Economy and Finance Ministers here, Tietmeyer
declined to say whether the February 22 Paris accord by the
Group of Five countries plus Canada included secret agreements
for stabilising currencies.
    But he noted the official communique said the participants
agreed to cooperate closely to foster stability of exchange
rates around current levels. "We're taking this sentence very
seriously," he said.
    Tietmeyer remarked that the dollar had hardly moved against
the mark since the meeting.
    He said a slowdown in West German economic growth had been
caused by sharp exchange rate swings and that the Paris
agreement should help in this respect.
    Economics Ministry State Secretary Otto Schlecht said the
Bonn government saw no current need for measures to bolster the
economy but was paying close attention to the slower growth and
had not ruled out "appropriate and timely" action if necessary.
    Schlecht and Tietmeyer were speaking ahead of a discussion
by the EC ministers of the latest EC Commission report on the
economic situation in the 12-nation bloc.
    The Commission has sharply revised down expected German
gross national product growth this year to two pct from 3.2 pct
predicted last autumn and says Bonn has the most room of any EC
country to stimulate economic activity.
    Schlecht said the upturn in West Germany's economy slowed
in the fourth quarter of last year and the first quarter of
1987. But he said there was no cumulative downwards trend in
view that would make quick remedial action necessary.
    He said a number of favourable indicators such as high
level of investment and a good climate for consumption meant a
recovery could be expected, while exports would pick up
slightly during the course of the year.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="NO" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="19830" NEWID="3408">
<DATE> 9-MAR-1987 17:49:16.81</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>belgium</D><D>spain</D><D>portugal</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS><D>ec</D></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   C G L
   f0005 reute
r f AM-COMMUNITY-BUTTER   03-09 0124</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>FUTURE OF EC BUTTER DISPOSAL SCHEME IN DOUBT</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    BRUSSELS, March 9 - </DATELINE><BODY>A 3.6 billion dlr plan to rid the
European Community (EC) of one mln tonnes of surplus butter is
in doubt as Spain and Portugal refuse to drop their opposition
to the scheme, diplomats said.
    The plan, proposed by the Community's executive Commission,
aims to level most of the EC's huge and costly butter mountain
by disposing of a total of 1.04 mln tonnes this year and next.
    But the officials said Spain and Portugal, which joined the
12-nation bloc at the beginning of last year, continued to
oppose the scheme at a meeting of EC finance ministers here.
    They argued they should not have to pay for the disposal of
surpluses created before they became EC members.
    The plan, already approved by farm ministers despite
opposition from Madrid and Lisbon, had been sent to finance
ministers for final approval.
    But the diplomats said the finance ministers instead
referred it back to the Commission, asking it to study possible
ways to solve the row as soon as possible.
    They said Spain and Portugal indicated they may go to the
European Court of Justice over the issue if the Commission did
not come up with a satisfactory solution.
    The scheme has also run into criticism from the EC's
financial watchdog, the Court of Auditors.
    The Court has said the plan is unsound because the
Commission wants member states to foot the bill until it starts
reimbursing them in four annual instalments from 1989.
    Diplomats said Spain and Portugal backed the court's view
and also complained that, under complex financial agreements
worked out when they joined the EC, they would get less back
later than if they were reimbursed now.
    Commission sources said it appeared the two countries were
holding out in a bid to squeeze some form of compensation out
of their partners but it was unclear how much longer they would
continue to block the scheme.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="19831" NEWID="3409">
<DATE> 9-MAR-1987 17:49:32.83</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>acq</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F
   f0006 reute
d f BC-BANCROFT-&lt;BCV>-FILES   03-09 0095</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>BANCROFT &lt;BCV> FILES SUIT AGAINST ZICO</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    NEW YORK, March 9 - </DATELINE><BODY>Bancroft Convertible Fund Inc said it
filed a lawsuit in federal court in Newark, N.J., seeking to
block a hostile 30 dlr a share takeover offer by &lt;Zico
Investment Holdings Inc.>
    Bancroft said the suit also names Michael B. Javett,
principal officer of Zico, and First Fidelity Bancorp's &lt;FFB>
First Fidelity Bank unit, the depositary for Zico's offer.
    Bancroft said the suit also names &lt;Georgeson and Co Inc>,
Zico's information agent, and &lt;Luthie Intercontinentale Inc>, a
Panamanian corporation.
    Bancroft said its complaint alleges that Zico's tender
offer materials include false and misleading information and
that the offer violates the Investment Company Act of 1940.
    The company said its stockholders approved proposals that
will insure that it remains independent.

 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="NO" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="19832" NEWID="3410">
<DATE> 9-MAR-1987 17:50:32.51</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>canada</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   E
   f0008 reute
u f BC-BELL-CANADA-(BCE),-LA   03-09 0115</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>BELL CANADA (BCE), LAVALIN TO BID ON MAP SERVICE</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    MONTREAL, March 9 - </DATELINE><BODY>&lt;Lavalin Bell Geomat>, a company owned
by Bell Canada Enterprises Inc and engineering company &lt;Lavalin
Inc>, plans a bid to take over the federal government's map
making service, Lavalin said.
    The service has an annual budget of about 130 mln Canadian
dlrs and includes the surveys and mapping and remote sensing
branches of the Energy, Mines, and Resources department, and
the hydrographic services of the Fisheries and Oceans
department, Lavalin president Bernard Lamarre said.
    Lamarre said company officials have held preliminary talks
with the government to discuss the possibility of taking over
the service.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="8845" NEWID="3932">
<DATE>11-MAR-1987 16:06:16.30</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   RM F A
   f0547 reute
r f BC-S/P-MAY-DOWNGRADE-CLA   03-11 0105</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>S/P MAY DOWNGRADE CLARK EQUIPMENT &lt;CKL></TITLE>
<DATELINE>    NEW YORK, March 11 - </DATELINE><BODY>Standard and Poor's said it may lower
its BBB-minus rating of Clark Equipment Co's 108 mln dlrs of
long-term debt because of weak industry fundamentals and the
company's plan to repurchase 70 mln dlrs worth of common stock.
    Despite a dramatic rationalization of its fork-lift truck,
axle and transmission, and construction equipment operations,
continuing intense competitive pressures are limiting Clark's
growth and profit potential, S and P said.
    The company may be forced to increase debt to achieve its
strategic acquisition goals, the rating agency added.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="8846" NEWID="3933">
<DATE>11-MAR-1987 16:06:25.36</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>acq</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D><D>hong-kong</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F
   f0548 reute
r f BC-CALMAT   03-11 0109</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>HONG KONG FIRM UPS CALMAT &lt;CZM> STAKE TO 9.8 PCT</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    WASHINGTON, March 11 - </DATELINE><BODY>Industrial Equity (Pacific) Ltd, a
Hong Kong investment firm, said it raised its stake in Calmat
Co to 1,480,830 shares, or 9.8 pct of the total outstanding
common stock, from 1,217,230 shares, or 8.0 pct.
    In a filing with the Securities and Exchange Commission,
Industrial Equity, which is principally owned by Brierley
Investments Ltd, a publicly held New Zealand firm, said it
bought 263,600 Calmat common shares between Feb 17 and March 9
for 13.1 mln dlrs.
    It has said it bought the stock for investment purposes,
but may raise its stake to 15 pct.
                    
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="8847" NEWID="3934">
<DATE>11-MAR-1987 16:07:09.55</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>acq</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F
   f0549 reute
r f BC-PARALAX-VIDEO-&lt;VIDO>   03-11 0104</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>PARALAX VIDEO &lt;VIDO> TO BUY AMERICAN VIDEO</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    NEW YORK, March 11 - </DATELINE><BODY>Paralax Video Enterprises Inc said it
signed a definitive agreement to buy &lt;American Video Group Inc>
for stock.
    According to the merger proposal, American Video
shareholders will receive about 287,700 restricted Paralax
shares, and warrants to buy another 318,600 restricted shares
at six dlrs a share. The warrants run for three years.
    In addition, it said holders of American Video convertible
debentures agreed to exchange their holdings for about 380,000
dlrs worth of Paralax stock.
    American Video operates stores in U.S. military bases.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="9145" NEWID="4232">
<DATE>12-MAR-1987 10:18:49.48</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>earn</D><D>crude</D><D>nat-gas</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F Y
   f0135 reute
r f BC-PHILLIPS-&lt;P>-TO-EMPHA   03-12 0105</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>PHILLIPS &lt;P> TO EMPHASIZE CASH FLOW TO PARE DEBT</TITLE>
<AUTHOR>    By Ted D'Afflisio, Reuters</AUTHOR>
<DATELINE>    NEW YORK, March 12 - </DATELINE><BODY>Phillips Petroleum Co will emphasize
improving its short-term cash flow this year to pare its debt,
C.J. "Pete" Silas, chairman, told Reuters in an interview.
    "Our priority is to get cash flow increased from the assets
already installed," he said, but he declined to estimate annual
cash flow for 1987.
    Analysts estimate Phillips" cash flow at over one billion
dlrs for 1987, while long term debt, which resulted from
restructuring to find off corporate raiders in 1985, hovers
about 5.9 billion dlrs as of December 1986.
     Silas said Phillips hope to achieve its goal by raising
the capital expenditures budget to develop its oil and gas
properties.
    "We plan to develop the properties with short-term high cash
flow prospects," he said. He projected a capital expenditure
budget of 730 mln dlrs, up from the 1986 expenditure of 655 mln
dlrs.
    Nearly half of that will be spent on exploration and
production, and most of that will be spend overseas, Silas
said.
    "Phillips' top priority in 1987 will be to get the
waterflooding in Norway and jack up the (Ekofisk) oil fields to
improve our ability to extract oil and increase earnings," Silas
said.
     Phillips estimates that the project, which is expected to
cost 1.5 billion dlrs, will increase recovery by 170 mln gross
barrels of oil over a period of 24 years.
    Phillips is also pursue opportunities in China where Silas
said he was seeking "a modification of terms with the Chinese
government to make oil discoveries (in the offshore Xijang
fields) commercially viable."
    In the U.S. Silas said Phillips hopes to get the Point
Arguello, Calif., field started up by the fourth quarter. "We
expect to start up the first platform then," Silas said.
    But emphasis on short-term cash flow has also forced the
company to part with several oil and gas assets.
    Phillips sold its interests in the T-Block in the U.K.
North Sea and U.S. reserves totaling about 1.3 billion dlrs in
1986 as part of a two billion dlrs asset sales program that is
now completed, Silas said.
     "We sold high cost producing assets. They were not good
value for us but possibly so for someone else," Silas said.
    Silas said the 1986 assets sales will not affect earnings
for the company.
    "Everything we are doing is to manage our cash flow and we
are using that to manage our debt. Even the asset sales, while
regrettable, were necessary to reduce debt," Silas said.
    He said no asset sales are planned this year as long as oil
prices don't fall sharply lower and stay at lower levels  for
several months. "Then, everyone would be looking at sales (of
assets), and we're no different from the others," Silas said.
    In other areas, Silas looks for improved earnings from
Phillips chemical operations, which provided 299 mln dlrs in
earnings for 1986, up from 219 mln dlrs in 1985.
    "This was our second best year pushed by a good supply and
demand balance for products, low feedstocks and energy costs
for our operations," Silas said, "In 1987 we think the market's
supply and demand balance will be just as good but feedstock
and energy costs will rise due to price recovery."
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="9146" NEWID="4233">
<DATE>12-MAR-1987 10:19:08.67</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>acq</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>canada</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   E F RM
   f0137 reute
r f BC-merrill-lynch-canada   03-12 0103</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>MERRILL LYNCH&lt;MER> CANADA MULLS BUYING BROKER</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    TORONTO, March 12 - </DATELINE><BODY>Merrill Lynch Canada Inc, wholly owned
by Merrill Lynch and Co, is considering acquiring another
Canadian securities company as the result of federal and
provincial government moves to lift investment dealer ownership
restrictions on June 30, according to a published report.
    "We're talking to a number of people," Merrill Lynch Canada
deputy chairman E. Duff Scott told The Toronto Star. "Whether
we're going to do something, I don't know," he said.
    A Merrill Lynch Canada spokesman declined to comment on the
newspaper report when queried.
    Scott did not disclose which investment dealers Merrill
Lynch Canada was considering acquiring, but the Toronto Star
quoted unidentified industry sources as saying serious
discussions have already been held with Burns Fry Ltd.
    Burns Fry chairman Jack Lawrence told the newspaper the
investment dealer has not made a final decision, but was
examining "three or four alternatives."
    Discussions between brokers about possible mergers is to be
expected pending industry deregulation, one investment industry
source, who asked not to be named, told Reuters.
    "It's silly not to take a look (at making a merger or
acquisition). If you're a businessman, you have to take a look,"
the industry source said.
    Under federal and provincial government regulations
expected to be in place by June 30, banks, trust companies and
foreign companies will be allowed to acquire existing
investment dealers or establish their own securities
subsidiaries.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="NO" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="9160" NEWID="4247">
<DATE>12-MAR-1987 10:26:49.07</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F
   f0175 reute
d f BC-LEWIS-LEHRMAN-TO-JOIN   03-12 0093</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>LEWIS LEHRMAN TO JOIN MORGAN STANLEY &lt;MS></TITLE>
<DATELINE>    NEW YORK, March 12 - </DATELINE><BODY>Morgan Stanley Group Inc said Lewis E.
Lehrman will join the firm as senior advisor as a directory of
Morgan Stanley Asset Management.
    It said Lehrman will concentrate on the growth and
development of Morgan Stanley's asset management business in
the U.S., Europe and Asia.
    Lehrman, the former president and chairman of the executive
committee at Rite Aid Corpo &lt;RAD>, ran against Mario Cuomo as
the Republican and Conservative Party Candidate for governor of
New York State in 1982.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="NO" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="9466" NEWID="4553">
<DATE>12-MAR-1987 16:46:24.74</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F
   f0566 reute
d f BC-ROCHESTER-GAS-&lt;RGS>-O   03-12 0093</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>ROCHESTER GAS &lt;RGS> OFFERED PRD SHARES</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    ROCHESTER, N.Y., March 12 - </DATELINE><BODY>Rochester Gas and Electric Corp
said 300,000 shares of 8.25 pct preferred stock, series R, will
be offered at 100 dlrs per share plus accrued dividends, if
any, from the date of the original issue.
    It said The First Boston Corp &lt;FBC> and &lt;E.F. Hutton and Co
Inc> are co-underwriters of the issue.
    It said net proceeds of the offering will be used to redeem
its 10.84 pct preferred stock, series G, which is currently
callable at 107 dlrs per share and for other corporate
purposes.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="10538" NEWID="5625">
<DATE>16-MAR-1987 15:02:18.60</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   A RM
   f3371 reute
r f BC-MOODY'S-MAY-DOWNGRADE   03-16 0108</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>MOODY'S MAY DOWNGRADE CONSECO &lt;CNC> DEBT</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    NEW YORK, March 16 - </DATELINE><BODY>Moody's Investors Service Inc said it
may downgrade Conseco Inc's 100 mln dlrs of debt.
    The rating agency cited Conseco's proposal to acquire
Western National Life Insurance Co from Beneficial Corp &lt;BNL>.
Moody's said its review would focus on the financing of the
deal, which will increase Conseco's size from 650 mln dlrs in
assets to about 2.7 billion dlrs.
    Moody's will also study the adequacy of projected earnings
and cash flow from Western National in relation to the
financing plan. Conseco currently carries B-1 senior
subordinated debentures and convertible debt.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="10539" NEWID="5626">
<DATE>16-MAR-1987 15:02:43.91</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D><D>brazil</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   A F RM
   f3374 reute
u f BC-MORGAN-&lt;JPM>-SAYS-BRA   03-16 0113</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>MORGAN &lt;JPM> SAYS BRAZIL NONACCRUALS MAY RISE</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    NEW YORK, March 16 - </DATELINE><BODY>J.P. Morgan and Co Inc said that
Brazil's recent suspension of interest payments on part of its
commercial bank debt may lift its nonaccrual loans this year.
    Morgan, which has over 1.9 billion dlrs of Brazilian debt,
said in its annual report, "it is possible that nonaccrual
loans to borrowers in Brazil could increase during 1987."
    However, a spokesman for Morgan told Reuters, "right now we
are still accruing interest and we have not yet decided what
will be done as of March 31."
    Citicorp &lt;CCI> said last week that 3.9 billion dlrs of
Brazilian loans may be put on a cash basis on March 31.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="10540" NEWID="5627">
<DATE>16-MAR-1987 15:07:10.06</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>earn</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F
   f3390 reute
r f BC-PHILIP-CROSBY-ASSOCIA   03-16 0085</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>PHILIP CROSBY ASSOCIATES &lt;PCA> EARNINGS DELAYED</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    WINTER PARK, Fla., March 16 - </DATELINE><BODY>Philip Crosby Associates Inc
said its fourth quarter and annual earnings report will be
delayed two more weeks.
    The company cited the recent in-house embezzlement and a
subsequent review by auditors of its international situation as
reason for the delay.
    Philip Crosby, however, said it believes its December
estimate calling for earnings per share between 10 cts and 15
cts, on revenues of 11 mln dlrs, was still valid.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="NO" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="10541" NEWID="5628">
<DATE>16-MAR-1987 15:07:26.71</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F
   f3391 reute
b f BC-/BALLY-MFG-&lt;BLY>-TAKI   03-16 0074</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>BALLY MFG &lt;BLY> TAKING HEALTH CLUB UNIT PUBLIC</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    CHICAGO, March 16 - </DATELINE><BODY>Bally Manufacturing Corp said its
Health and Tennis Corp filed with the Securities and Exchange
Commission for an initial public offering of 5,800,000 shares
of common stock and a concurrent offering of 50 mln dlrs of
20-year convertible subordinated debentures.
    The company said it expects the initial public offering
price to be between 13 dlrs and 15 dlrs a share.
    Upon completion of the offering, Bally said it will own 76
pct of Bally's Health and Tennis Corp.
    Bally said Drexel Burnham Lambert Inc and Paine Webber Inc
will represent underwriters of the offering, and Drexel will
underwrite the debenture offering.
    Bally's Health and Tennis Corp operates more than 250
fitness centers and has about 1,800,000 members.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="11980" NEWID="7067">
<DATE>19-MAR-1987 09:07:14.88</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>crude</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>canada</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   E F Y
   f0763 reute
r f BC-roxy   03-19 0095</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>CANADIAN ROXY IN NEW ALBERTA OIL DISCOVERY</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    CALGARY, Alberta, March 19 - </DATELINE><BODY>&lt;Canadian Roxy Petroleum Ltd>
said a new oil discovery in the Peerless Lake area of
north-central Alberta is capable of flowing at over 1,000
barrels of oil a day from a lower zone and more than 1,500
barrels a day from a separate upper zone.
    Canadian Roxy has a 35 pct interest in the five-year
royalty free well, known as the Canadian Roxy et Al Trout
A14-8-89-3 W5M. Texaco Canada Inc holds 25 pct, MLC Oil and Gas
Ltd 15 pct, Northstar Energy Corp 13.5 pct and Tricentrol Oils
Ltd 11.5 pct.
    Canadian Roxy said drilling has started on a follow-up
exploratory well about one mile northwest of the discovery
well.
    The company said it holds a net 6,500 acres in the vicinity
of the discovery and a seismic program is underway to evaluate
further drilling opportunities.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="11981" NEWID="7068">
<DATE>19-MAR-1987 09:08:28.40</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>acq</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F
   f0765 reute
u f BC-WASTE-MANAGEMENT&lt;WMX>   03-19 0079</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>WASTE MANAGEMENT&lt;WMX> TO RAISE CHEMLAWN&lt;CHEM>BID</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    OAK BROOK, ILL., March 19 - </DATELINE><BODY>Waste Management Inc said it
sent a letter to the ChemLawn Corp board, saying it is prepared
to increase its bid for ChemLawn to 33 dlrs a share,
from 27 dlrs, if ChemLawn promptly negotiates and executes a
simple two-step merger agreement containing only essential
covenants and conditions.
    Upon such an agreement, Waste Management said, it would
amend its 27 dlrs a share cash tender offer.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="11982" NEWID="7069">
<DATE>19-MAR-1987 09:16:10.78</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F A RM
   f0785 reute
u f BC-AMERICAN-CAN-&lt;AC>-FIL   03-19 0058</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>AMERICAN CAN &lt;AC> FILES 500 MLN DLR SHELF OFFER</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    GREENWICH, Conn., March 19 - </DATELINE><BODY>American Can cop said it has
filed a shelf registration covering 500 mln dlrs of debt
securities to be issued from time to time.
    It said proceeds will be used for general corporate
purposes, which could include acquisitions, business
investments or debt repayment.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="11983" NEWID="7070">
<DATE>19-MAR-1987 09:17:31.25</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>jobs</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   A RM
   f0793 reute
u f BC-U.S.-FIRST-TIME-JOBLE   03-19 0080</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>u.s. first time jobless claims fell in week</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    WASHINGTON, March 19 - </DATELINE><BODY>New applications for unemployment
insurance benefits fell to a seasonally adjusted 340,000 in the
week ended March 7 from 373,000 in the prior week, the Labor
Department said.
    The number of people actually receiving benefits under
regular state programs totaled 2,507,000 in the week ended Feb
28, the latest period for which that figure was available.
    That was up from 2,477,000 the previous week.
     
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="11984" NEWID="7071">
<DATE>19-MAR-1987 09:17:56.77</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>cocoa</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>uk</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS><D>icco</D></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   C T
   f0796 reute
b f BC-COCOA-DELEGATES-OPTIM   03-19 0098</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>COCOA DELEGATES OPTIMISTIC ON BUFFER STOCK RULES</TITLE>
<AUTHOR>    By Lisa Vaughan, Reuters</AUTHOR>
<DATELINE>    LONDON, March 19 - </DATELINE><BODY>Hopes mounted for an agreement on cocoa
buffer stock rules at an International Cocoa Organization,
ICCO, council meeting which opened here today, delegates said.
    Both producer and consumer ICCO members said after the
opening session that prospects for an agreement on the cocoa
market support mechanism were improving.
    "The chances are very good as of now of getting buffer stock
rules by the end of next week," Ghanaian delegate and producer
spokesman Mama Mohammed told journalists.
    Consumer spokesman Peter Baron called the tone of the
negotiations "optimistic and realistic."
    The ICCO council failed to agree on buffer stock rules when
a new International Cocoa Agreement came into force in January,
with deep differences of opinion precluding serious discussions
on the matter at that time. The existing buffer stock of about
100,000 tonnes of cocoa was frozen, with a funds balance of 250
mln dlrs.
    The ICCO made buffer stock rules negotiations a priority at
this semi-annual council meeting in order to stop the slide in
world cocoa prices.
    Consumers and producers agreed yesterday on the principles
as a basis for negotiations.
    The council broke for lunch, and reconvenes at 1500 hrs. A
working group which has been meeting since Monday will tackle
the buffer stock rules issue again at 1600 hrs, when ICCO
executive director Kobena Erbynn presents a fleshed-out version
of a draft proposal he prepared earlier this week, delegates
said.
    Mohammed said delegates will have a much clearer indication
of prospects for an accord after details of the rules are
elaborated by Erbynn, and after producers and consumers meet
separately later today to examine the scheme.
    The draft proposal included three principles: a limit to
non- member cocoa comprising the buffer stock, an offer system
for buying buffer stock cocoa, and price differentials to be
paid for various cocoas making up the buffer stock, delegates
said.
    During the morning council session, the Ivory Coast
delegation gave "an open minded statement" that it is willing to
work out a buffer stock rules solution which could come into
effect as soon as possible, Baron said.
    Ivorian Agriculture Minister Denis Bra Kanon, chairman of
the ICCO council, was now expected to arrive in London Monday
to attend the talks, Baron said. Vice chairman Sir Denis Henry
of Grenada chaired the meeting in his place.
    Soviet and East German delegates did not attend the council
session because of a conflicting International Sugar
Organization meeting today, but could arrive this afternoon,
delegates said.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="11985" NEWID="7072">
<DATE>19-MAR-1987 09:18:03.59</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>earn</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F
   f0797 reute
r f BC-STUARTS-DEPARTMENT-ST   03-19 0053</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>STUARTS DEPARTMENT STORES &lt;STUS> 4TH QTR NET</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    HOPKINTON, Mass., March 19 - </DATELINE><BODY>Ended Jan 31
    Shr one ct vs 31 cts
    Net 29,000 vs 1,350,000
    Revs 43.7 mln vs 32.4 mln
    Year
    Shr 29 cts vs 62 cts
    Net 1,251,000 vs 2,520,000
    Revs 129.9 mln vs 96.1 mln
    NOTE: Full name Stuarts Department Stores Inc.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="13165" NEWID="7644">
<DATE>20-MAR-1987 09:20:28.18</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>acq</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F Y
   f0802 reute
b f BC-OHIO-EDISON-&lt;OEC>-SEL   03-20 0112</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>OHIO EDISON &lt;OEC> SELLS 30 PCT OF NUCLEAR INTEREST</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    AKRON, Ohio, March 20 - </DATELINE><BODY>Ohio Edison Co said it has
completed the sale and leaseback of 30 pct of its 30 pct
interest in Unit One of the Perry Nuclear Power Plant,
receiving 509 mln dlrs for the interest.
    The utility said the share of its interest in the 1,205
megawatt generating plant was sold to a group of institutional
investors which leased it back to the company for a period of
about 29 years at a negotiated lease payment rate.
    Ohio Edison said the proceeds will be used to finance the
rest of its 1987 construction program and repay bank loans
incurred for the retirement of high-interest long-term debt.
    Ohio Edison did not detail the lease payments, but it said
the "payments will reduce the amount of revenue the company
will need to cover our investment in Perry, which translates
into savings for our customers."
    The utility said it projects the financing could reduce the
amount of annual revenue needed by about 20 mln dlrs. It plans
on filing a rate application with the Public Utilities
Commission of Ohio to recover the Perry costs later this year.
    It said the sale and leaseback was attractive to the
investors because they could take quicker advantage of tax
benefits than the utility could.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="13166" NEWID="7645">
<DATE>20-MAR-1987 09:22:03.31</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>gold</D><D>silver</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   M
   f0803 reute
u f BC-GEODOME-SETS-IDAHO-GO   03-20 0141</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>GEODOME SETS IDAHO GOLD/SILVER MINE CONSTRUCTION</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    HAILEY, Idaho, March 20 - </DATELINE><BODY>Geodome Resources Ltd said
following receipt of a feasibility study from Raytheon Co's
Stearns Catalytic unit it will proceed with construction and
pre-production stripping at its Sunbeam Mine in Custer County,
Idaho, as quickly as possible.
    The company said the study found proven ore reserves of
3,302,000 short tons grading 0.077 ounce of gold per ton. It
said the mine will operate at a rate of 626,000 tons of ore per
year, with higher-grade ore being mined in the first three
years for a rapid payback of capital costs.
    It said the feasibility study calls for gold production
averaging 41,000 ounces a year for the life of the mine and
50,000 ounces a year over the first three years, with 99,000
ounces of silver per year being produced over the mine life.
    Capital costs would be 22.3 mln dlrs with all-new equipment
and 500,000 to one mln dlrs less with used equipment, the firm
said. It said the mine would be operated by a contract miner
but the associated mill by Geodome.
    Geodome said a new ore zone discovered last summer is not
included in reserve calculations. It said eight of the nine
holes drilled there have an average grade of 0.046 ounce of
gold and 2.1 ounces of silver per ton.
    Also excluded are reserves of 1,400,000 tons of low-grade
material that could be milled profitably at 425 dlrs a ton for
gold. The feasibility study used a 350 dlr gold price.
    Geodome said operating costs of the mine will average 201
dlr per ounce of gold for the mine life and 171 dlrs for the
first three years, in constant dollars.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="13167" NEWID="7646">
<DATE>20-MAR-1987 09:22:35.25</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D><D>australia</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F
   f0805 reute
u f BC-QINTEX-SAYS-PRINCEVIL   03-20 0091</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>QINTEX SAYS PRINCEVILLE &lt;PVDC> IN CREDIT DEAL</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    NEW YORK, March 20 - </DATELINE><BODY>&lt;Qintex Ltd> of Brisbane said it has
arranged for a leading Australian financial institution it did
not name to provide Princeville Development Corp with the
letter of credit required by the terms of Qintex's proposed
acquisition of Princeville.
    The company also said through yesterday, when its tender
offer for 3,300,000 Princeville shares was to have expired, it
had received over seven mln Princeville shares in the bid,
which has been extended until March 23 at 1800 EST.
    Qintex said the letter of credit is to insure payment of
Princeville's contingent subordinated notes that would be
distributed to shareholders of record on the date immediately
following completion of the tender offer.
    The company said it believes the conditions of the
commitment letter will be satisfactory to Princeville.  It said
Princeville had previously held talks with a financial
institution on obtaining a letter of credit but was unable to
reach mutually acceptable terms.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="13168" NEWID="7647">
<DATE>20-MAR-1987 09:23:01.72</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>earn</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F
   f0807 reute
u f BC-STANLEY-INTERIORS-&lt;ST   03-20 0051</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>STANLEY INTERIORS &lt;STHF> SAYS RESULTS REDUCED</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    STANLEYTOWN, Va., March 20 - </DATELINE><BODY>Stanley Interiors Corp said
its first quarter shipments and operating income were lower
than expected due to snowstorms in January and February that
forced the closing of some of its manufacturing facilities for
up to six days.
    Stanley said, however, that any reduction in first quarter
operating income will be offset by reduced interest expense and
that first quarter net income will be about flat with first
quarter 1986 net income of 14 cts a share, or 286,000 dlrs.
    Stanely also said the first quarter's sales losses would be
made up by shipments in the second quarter.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="13584" NEWID="8063">
<DATE>21-MAR-1987 04:11:13.22</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>ipi</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>taiwan</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   RM
   f0015 reute
r f BC-TAIWAN-INDUSTRIAL-OUT   03-21 0114</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>TAIWAN INDUSTRIAL OUTPUT FALLS, CURRENCY BLAMED</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    TAIPEI, March 21 - </DATELINE><BODY>Taiwan's industrial production index,
fell, largely as the result of the rising Taiwan dollar, by
8.18 pct to 140.06 (base 1981) in February from a revised
152.53 in January, the Economy Ministry said.
    It was the second consecutive monthly fall, after dropping
nine pct in January, but it was still 26.49 pct up on February
1986 following a very extended rise last year.
    The January figure was revised from a preliminary 154.82.
    A ministry official attributed the decline to falling
production of non-metal products, textiles and transportation
equipment, and less mining and house construction.
    The official said the decline was also caused by falling
exports in February due to the climb of the Taiwan dollar,
which has made Taiwanese products more expensive.
    He expected the decline to continue in the next few months
because of further appreciation of the local dollar against the
U.S. Currency.
    The Taiwan dollar advanced more than 15 pct against the
U.S. Dollar since September 1985. It closed at 34.40 to the
U.S. Dollar today, and is expected to rise to about 32 to the
dollar by the end of this year, foreign bankers and economists
said.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="13794" NEWID="8273">
<DATE>23-MAR-1987 10:21:50.76</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>trade</D><D>cotton</D><D>grain</D><D>corn</D><D>wheat</D><D>oilseed</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   C G
   f1055 reute
u f BC-/MARKET-LOAN-COULD-BE   03-23 0134</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>MARKET LOAN COULD BE PINNED TO U.S. TRADE BILL</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    BOCA RATON, Fla., March 23 - </DATELINE><BODY>Sen. David Pryor, D-Ark., said
he was considering amending the Senate Finance Committee's
trade bill with a provision to require a marketing loan for
soybeans, corn and wheat.
    Pryor told the Futures Industry Association that there was
great reluctance among members of the Senate Agriculture
Committee to reopen the 1985 farm bill, and that a marketing
loan might have a better chance in the Finance panel.
    The Arkansas senator said the marketing loan -- which in
effect allows producers to pay back their crop loans at the
world price -- had led to a 300 pct increase in U.S. cotton
exports in 14 months and a 72 pct increase in rice exports.
    Pryor serves on both the Senate Finance and Agriculture
Committees.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="13840" NEWID="8319">
<DATE>23-MAR-1987 11:20:56.51</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>ship</D><D>grain</D><D>oilseed</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>netherlands</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   G
   f1331 reute
r f BC-ROTTERDAM-GRAIN-HANDL   03-23 0101</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>ROTTERDAM GRAIN HANDLER SAYS PORT BALANCE ROSE</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    ROTTERDAM, March 23 - </DATELINE><BODY>Graan Elevator Mij (GEM) said its
balance in port of grains, oilseeds and derivatives rose to
70,000 tonnes on March 21 compared with 10,000 a week earlier
after arrivals of 192,000 tonnes and discharges of 132,000
tonnes last week.
    The balance comprised 25,000 tonnes of grains plus oilseeds
and 45,000 tonnes of derivatives.
    This week's estimated arrivals total 487,000 tonnes, of
which 107,000 are grains/oilseeds and 380,000 derivatives.
    The figures cover around 95 pct of Rotterdam traffic in the
products concerned.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="14623" NEWID="9102">
<DATE>24-MAR-1987 18:45:24.42</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>acq</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   E F
   f2793 reute
r f BC-FLEET-TO-ACQUIRE-ASSE   03-24 0088</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>FLEET TO ACQUIRE ASSETS OF MARK IV &lt;IV> UNIT</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    ST. CATHARINES, Ontario, March 24 - </DATELINE><BODY>&lt;Fleet Aerospace Corp>
said it agreed in principle to acquire the assets and
operations of the Engineered Magnetics division of Gulton
Industries Inc, a unit of Mark IV Industries Inc.
    Terms were undisclosed.
    Los Angeles-based Engineered Magnetics designs and produces
custom power conversion systems mainly for use in the defense
and aerospace industries. Its revenues for the year ended
February 28 totaled about 20 mln Canadian dlrs.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="14628" NEWID="9107">
<DATE>24-MAR-1987 18:56:31.28</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>money-supply</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>australia</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   RM
   f2809 reute
u f BC-AUSTN-FEB-ANNUAL-M3-M   03-24 0062</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>AUSTN FEB ANNUAL M3 MONEY SUPPLY RISES 11.2 PCT</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    Sydney, March 25 - </DATELINE><BODY>The annual growth of Australia's m3
money supply rose by 11.2 pct in the year ended February
compared with January's 10.7 pct, the Reserve Bank said.
    This was down from 14.0 pct in February last year.
    In February m3 rose by 0.6 pct compared with 0.8 in January
and a February 1986 rise of 0.1 pct.
 More
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="16129" NEWID="10608">
<DATE>28-MAR-1987 01:58:48.19</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>trade</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D><D>japan</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   RM
   f2725 reute
r f BC-JAPAN'S-CHIP-MAKERS-A   03-28 0092</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>JAPAN'S CHIP MAKERS ANGERED BY U.S. SANCTION PLANS</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    TOKYO, March 28 - </DATELINE><BODY>Japanese computer chip makers reacted
angrily to news the United States plans to take retaliatory
action against them for allegedly failing to live up to an
agreement on trade in computer microchips.
    Electronic Industries Association of Japan (EIAJ) Chairman
Shoichi Saba stated: "EIAJ believes that it is premature and
even irrational to attempt an assessment of the impact of the
agreement and our efforts to comply with it only six months
after concluding the agreement."
    "We urge U.S. Governmental authorities to reconsider the
decision made, to evaluate fairly the results of Japanese
efforts in implementing the objectives of the agreement, and to
resist emotional biases," he said.
    Yesterday, Washington announced plans to slap as much as
300 mln dlrs in tariffs on Japanese imports in retaliation for
what is sees as Japan's failure to comply with the terms of the
pact.
    The agreement, struck late last year after months of heated
negotiations, called on Japan to stop selling cut-price chips
on world markets and to buy more American-made semiconductors.
    To salvage the pact, Tokyo has instructed its chip makers
to slash production and has helped establish a multi-lateral
organisation designed to promote chip imports.
    Saba said that Japanese chip companies have pledged three
mln dlrs over the next five years to the new organisation and
expressed regret that no American company has seen fit to join.
    "This suggests that American semiconductor manufacturers may
not be really interested in participating in the Japanese
market," he said.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="16739" NEWID="10678">
<DATE>30-MAR-1987 00:50:32.37</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>nickel</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>japan</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   M C
   f0026 reute
u f BC-SUMITOMO-MINING-&lt;SMIT   03-30 0101</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>SUMITOMO MINING &lt;SMIT.T> RAISES NICKEL OUTPUT</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    TOKYO, March 30 - </DATELINE><BODY>Sumitomo Metal Mining Co said it will
raise its monthly nickel output to around 1,750 tonnes from
April 1 from 1,650 now because of increased domestic demand,
mainly from stainless steel makers.
    Sumitomo produced 1,800 tonnes of a nickel a month until
end-1986, but cut output in January because of stagnant demand,
a company official said.
    Calendar 1987 production is likely to fall to around 20,000
tonnes from 22,000 in 1986 as a result of the first quarter
reduction, he said.
    Sumitomo is Japan's only nickel producer.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="NO" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="16741" NEWID="10680">
<DATE>30-MAR-1987 00:55:38.27</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>japan</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS><D>ec</D></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F
   f0028 reute
u f BC-JAPAN-VEHICLE-EXPORTS   03-30 0085</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>JAPAN VEHICLE EXPORTS FALL IN FEBRUARY</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    TOKYO, March 30 - </DATELINE><BODY>Japanese vehicle exports fell 8.2 pct in
February from January to 530,066, the Japan Automobile
Manufacturers Association said.
    February exports fell 6.8 pct from a year earlier after a
6.8 pct year-on-year rise in January, the first growth since
June 1986, when they rose 4.4 pct from a year earlier.
    February exports included 361,285 cars, down 6.3 pct from a
year earlier, 165,770 trucks, down 8.6 pct, and 3,011 buses, up
51.4 pct.
    Exports to the U.S. Fell to 226,942 in February from
259,272 a year earlier, while those to the European Community
rose to 141,095 from 121,050.
    The EC figure included 63,387 vehicles to West Germany, up
from 41,821, but exports to Britain fell to 20,554 from 28,536.
    Shipments to South-east Asia fell to 33,957 from 41,960 and
those to the Middle East fell to 15,828 from 25,278.
    Japan's motorcycle exports rose 18 pct from January to
177,115 in February, but fell 25.9 pct from a year earlier, the
12th consecutive year-on-year drop.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="16745" NEWID="10684">
<DATE>30-MAR-1987 01:03:30.23</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>money-fx</D><D>dlr</D><D>yen</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>japan</D><D>uk</D><D>usa</D><D>france</D><D>canada</D><D>west-germany</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE><D>nakasone</D><D>miyazawa</D></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   RM
   f0036 reute
b f BC-G-6-WANTS-TO-HOLD-DLR   03-30 0101</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>G-6 WANTS TO HOLD DLR ABOVE 150 YEN - NAKASONE</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    TOKYO, March 30 - </DATELINE><BODY>Prime Minister Yasuhiro Nakasone said
that Japan and other industrialized nations committed
themselves in Paris last month to stabilize the dollar above
150 yen.
    He told a Lower House Budget Committee in Parliament that
the six nations have taken measures, including market
intervention, to support the dollar above that level.
    Finance Minister Kiichi Miyazawa told the same committee
that the six - Britain, Canada, France, Japan, the U.S. And
West Germany - had intervened aggressively since the dollar
fell below 150 yen.
    Miyazawa said major nations are trying hard to stabilize
exchange rates.
    Asked if there had been any change in the fundamentals of
each nation since the February 22 Paris accord, he said he did
not think the fundamentals themselves had changed
substantially.
    But he said the market is sensitively looking at what is
happening in major nations. He did not elaborate.
    Miyazawa added that it was difficult to say why there has
been such speculative dollar selling in the market.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="NO" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="17013" NEWID="10952">
<DATE>30-MAR-1987 13:33:17.30</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>nigeria</D><D>uk</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   C T G M
   f2024 reute
r f BC-NIGERIA-TO-ISSUE-1.5   03-30 0146</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>NIGERIA TO ISSUE 1.5 BILLION DLRS OF NOTES</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    LONDON, March 30 - </DATELINE><BODY>Nigeria will issue April 7 1.5 billion
dlrs in short-term promissory notes to its uninsured trade
creditors in connection with existing arrears on those debts,
Law Debenture Trust Corp Plc said as trustee for the notes.
    It said Nigeria also plans to hold talks with a newly
appointed representative for those creditors fairly soon, and
that Nigeria will call "at an early date" an extraordinary
meeting of noteholders, including holders of the new notes. The
purpose of that meeting will be to consider a resolution to the
arrears on the trade debt and the promissory notes.
    Nigeria missed the first principal payment due on the notes
last autumn and another payment of about 30 mln dlrs that was
due in early January because of a cash shortage, which stemmed
partly from the drop in oil prices last year.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="1529" NEWID="12453">
<DATE> 2-APR-1987 06:31:41.55</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>money-fx</D><D>interest</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>uk</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   RM
   f0530 reute
b f BC-U.K.-MONEY-MARKET-GIV   04-02 0112</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>U.K. MONEY MARKET GIVEN 345 MLN STG ASSISTANCE</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    LONDON, April 2 - </DATELINE><BODY>The Bank of England said it had provided
the money market with 345 mln stg help in the morning session.
This compares with its forecast of a shortage of around 800 mln
stg in the system today.
    The central bank made outright purchases of bank bills
comprising 58 mln stg in band one at 9-7/8 pct, 227 mln stg in
band two at 9-13/16 pct, 56 mln stg in band three at 9-3/4 pct
and four mln stg in band four at 9-11/16 pct.
    Dealers noted that this was the first time bills in band
four, which have a maturity of between two and three months,
have been dealt in the market since mid-February.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="1530" NEWID="12454">
<DATE> 2-APR-1987 06:33:33.01</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>acq</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>uk</D><D>japan</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   RM
   f0533 reute
u f BC-CABLE-UNIMPRESSED-BY   04-02 0108</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>CABLE UNIMPRESSED BY NEW JAPANESE TELECOMS OFFER</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    LONDON, April 2 - </DATELINE><BODY>Cable and Wireless Plc &lt;CAWL.L> said new
proposals unveiled by Japan for it to become a core member of a
merged telecommunications firm to compete for
telecommunications contracts did not remove the group's
objections.
    The suggestions by Federation of Economic Organisations
official Fumio Watanabe was a formal announcement of proposals
made earlier this week and reported in the Japanese press.
    Cable has a 20 pct stake in one of the two groups trying to
compete against Japan's &lt;Kokusai Denshin Denwa Co Ltd> which
monopolises Japan's overseas telephone business.
    But a Cable spokesman said it still believed a merger of
the two consortia would be impracticable. "They are like oil and
water," he said.
    The Japanese authorities want only one competitor and have
proposed that the two consortia band together. The issue has
been taken up by the British government as a test case on the
openness of Japanese markets. Watanabe's latest proposals said
that the eight core companies of the new group should have
equal share holdings but added that they could work out the
precise percentages amongst themselves.
    The reports earlier this week said that Cable would be
offered a five pct stake, up from an originally proposed three
pct.
    Despite the apparent differences in stakes offered, the
Cable spokesman said the two offers appeared to be essentially
the same.
    Cable shares at 1100 GMT were quoted nine pence firmer at
374p.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="1844" NEWID="12875">
<DATE> 3-APR-1987 09:57:37.05</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>reserves</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>west-germany</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 

   RM
   f0965 reute
u f BC-BUNDESBANK-GROSS-RESE   04-03 0100</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>BUNDESBANK GROSS RESERVES RISE AT MARCH CLOSE</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    FRANKFURT, April 3 - </DATELINE><BODY>The Bundesbank's gross currency
reserves rose 300 mln marks in the last week of March to 104.9
billion marks, the Bundesbank said in a statement.
    At the same time its foreign liabilities rose 100 mln to
22.8 billion, producing a rise in net reserves of 200 mln to
82.2 billion on March 31.
    The Bundesbank provided banks with liquidity in the fourth
March week by disbursing funds in the money market via
government-owned banks. Banks took up the Bundesbank's standing
offer of treasury bills to place excess liquidity.
    Banks received more liquidity through routine month-end
payments by public authorities as well as expansionary market
factors than was lost through the 2.3 billion mark rise in cash
in circulation to 122.3 billion, the Bundesbank said.
    But banks had to draw heavily on the Lombard emergency
financing facility due to month-end tightness, borrowing 5.3
billion marks.
    Overall, banks' holdings at the Bundesbank rose 10.2
billion marks to 58.5 billion at the end of the month,
averaging 50.9 billion in the whole of March.
    The minimum reserve requirement for March, before deduction
of banks' cash holdings, was set at 61 billion marks.
    Public authorities' net holdings at the Bundesbank fell to
2.2 billion marks in the last March week from 4.4 billion the
week before. The federal states' holdings fell 2.6 billion to
2.4 billion.
    The federal government's holdings rose 700 mln marks to 5.1
billion.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="NO" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="1850" NEWID="12881">
<DATE> 3-APR-1987 10:08:08.34</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>canada</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 

   E F
   f1021 reute
r f BC-algoma-steel-has-no   04-03 0100</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>ALGOMA STEEL HAS NO REASON FOR SHARE PRICE RISE</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    SAULT STE MARIE, Ontario, April 3 - </DATELINE><BODY>&lt;Algoma Steel Corp Ltd>
said there were no specific developments to explain the recent
increase in its share price and there were no announcements
planned or anticipated.
    The company said it made the statement at the request of
the Toronto Stock Exchange.
    Algoma said it continues to achieve cost reductions and
there is a limited improvement in market demand for the
company's steel products.
    Algoma common closed yesterday in Toronto at 18-1/2, up
2-3/4, and was trading today at 18-1/4, down 1/4.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="1852" NEWID="12883">
<DATE> 3-APR-1987 10:15:50.25</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>acq</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 

   F
   f1051 reute
b f BC-K-MART-&lt;KM>-SELLING-K   04-03 0066</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>K MART &lt;KM> SELLING KRESGE TO MCCRORY</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    TROY, MICH., April 3 - </DATELINE><BODY>K mart Corp said it agreed to sell
most of the U.S. Kresge and Jupiter stores to McCrory Corp, a
subsidiary of privately held Rapid American Corp.
    It said the agreement covers 76 stores in 21 states
including inventory and fixtures. The price depends on the
amount of the inventory that will be in the stores on the
closing date.
    K mart said it will continue to operate the stores until
early June, when McCrory will take over with no interruption of
service.
    The newly acquired Kresge and Jupiter stores will be
renamed McCrory 5 and 10. McCrory currently operates 1,250
stores in 38 states.

 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="1853" NEWID="12884">
<DATE> 3-APR-1987 10:16:32.53</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>belgium</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 

   RM
   f1055 reute
u f BC-BELGIAN-STATE-LOAN-RA   04-03 0059</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>BELGIAN STATE LOAN RAISES 168.8 BILLION FRANCS</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    BRUSSELS, April 3 - </DATELINE><BODY>The latest Belgian state loan,
subscriptions for which closed today, raised a total of 168.8
billion francs, a finance ministry spokesman said.
    The eight-year, eight pct domestic loan which was priced at
par was originally expected by the ministry to raise 150
billion francs.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="1854" NEWID="12885">
<DATE> 3-APR-1987 10:20:12.58</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>earn</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 

   F
   f1074 reute
u f BC-TANDY-&lt;TAN>-3RD-QUART   04-03 0106</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>TANDY &lt;TAN> 3RD QUARTER REVENUES UP 12 PCT</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    FORT WORTH, Texas, April 3 - </DATELINE><BODY>Tandy Corp said consolidated
sales and operating revenues for the third quarter, ended March
31, totaled nearly 776.0 mln dlrs, up 12 pct from 693.4 mln
dlrs last year.
    The company said third quarter earnings will be released in
the latter part of April.
    Tandy said March sales and oprating revenues totaled 164.4
mln dlrs, up 11 pct from March 1986's 238.8 mln dlrs.
    It said U.S. retail operations revenues rose to 225.8 mln
dlrs last month from 202.7 mln dlrs a year earlier. Sales of
U.S. stores in existence more than one year increased 10 pct.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="1855" NEWID="12886">
<DATE> 3-APR-1987 10:21:46.19</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>earn</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 

   F
   f1078 reute
u f BC-PHILIP-MORRIS-&lt;MO>-UP   04-03 0110</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>PHILIP MORRIS &lt;MO> UP ON RECOMMENDATIONS</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    NEW YORK, April 3 - </DATELINE><BODY>The stock of Philip Morris Cos rose
today following recommendations by First Boston Corp and Morgan
Stanley and Co, traders said.
    Philip Morris gained 1-3/4 to 88-1/4.
    First Boston's analyst was unavailable for comment.
    Morgan Stanley's David Hill said he just assumed coverage
of Philip Morris and placed it on his recommended list becasue
of its attractive earnings growth and because the stock is
selling at a discount to the market based on Morgan's figures.
Hill expects Morris to earn 7.75 dlrs a share this year and
9.50 dlrs in 1988. In 1986, Morris earned 6.20 dlrs a share.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="1859" NEWID="12890">
<DATE> 3-APR-1987 10:24:29.36</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>acq</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 

   F
   f1087 reute
r f BC-DU-PONT-&lt;DD>-TO-SELL   04-03 0112</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>DU PONT &lt;DD> TO SELL CLEVELAND PLANT</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    WILMINGTON, Del., April 3 - </DATELINE><BODY>Du Pont Co said it agreed to
sell its Cleveland chemical plant, the oldest site currently
operated by the company, to two employees.
    Terms were not disclosed.
    Closing is expected in the second quarter, following
approval of definitive agreements.
    Products made at the plant represent less than 1/10 of one
pct of Du Pont's annual sales, it said. Quilon chrome complexes
and Volan bonding agents will be supplied by the plant to Du
Pont under contract.
    Established in 1866, the plant was acquired by Du Pont in
1928. The plant no longer fits the company's long-term
strategy, Du Pont said
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="1860" NEWID="12891">
<DATE> 3-APR-1987 10:26:50.27</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>interest</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>spain</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 

   RM
   f1096 reute
u f BC-SPAIN-RAISES-CALL-MON   04-03 0090</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>SPAIN RAISES CALL MONEY RATE TO 14.5 PCT</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    MADRID, April 3 - </DATELINE><BODY>The Bank of Spain said it raised its rate
for overnight call money to 14.5 pct from 14 pct with immediate
effect at today's daily auction for assistance funds.
    The move followed comments yesterday by central bank
governor Mariano Rubio, who said money supply growth was too
fast.
    The bank said later that it was leaving its rate for
special assistance funds from its second window unchanged at 16
pct, surprising operators who had expected an increase there
too.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="NO" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="1861" NEWID="12892">
<DATE> 3-APR-1987 10:28:36.70</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 

   F
   f1104 reute
b f BC-VOLKSWAGEN-LATE-MARCH   04-03 0073</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>VOLKSWAGEN LATE MARCH U.S. SALES LOWER</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    TROY, Mich., April 3 - </DATELINE><BODY>Volkswagen of America Inc, the U.S.
arm of Volkswagen AG, said its domestic car sales for late
March fell to 2,145 vehicles, from 3,342 vehicles for the same
period in 1986.
    Volkswagen added that for the month of March it sold 4,324
vehicles, down from 6,198 last year.
    For the year-to-date, Volkswagen said it sold 10,951
vehicles, versus 18,392 last year-to-date.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="1862" NEWID="12893">
<DATE> 3-APR-1987 10:33:18.03</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>earn</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 

   F
   f1128 reute
u f BC-FEDERAL-CO-&lt;FFF>-3RD   04-03 0054</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>FEDERAL CO &lt;FFF> 3RD QTR FEB 28 NET</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    MEMPHIS, April 3 -
    </DATELINE><BODY>Shr 1.00 dlr vs 34 cts
    Net 16.9 mln vs 5,696,000
    Revs 371.3 mln vs 303.2 mln
    Avg shrs 16.9 mln vs 16.3 mln
    Nine mths
    Shr 3.55 dlrs vs 1.66 dlrs
    Net 59.3 mln vs 27.1 mln
    Revs 1.02 billion vs 912.8 mln
    Avg shrs 16.7 mln vs 16.3 mln
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="NO" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="1863" NEWID="12894">
<DATE> 3-APR-1987 10:34:28.90</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 

   F
   f1136 reute
r f BC-AMC-&lt;AMO>-TO-INSPECT   04-03 0101</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>AMC &lt;AMO> TO INSPECT 20,000 VEHICLES</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    SOUTHFIELD, MICH., April 3 - </DATELINE><BODY>American Motors Corp said it
will ask Jeep dealers to inspect about 20,000 Cherokee,
Wagoneer and Comanche vehicles equipped with 4.0-liter,
6-cylinder engines to determine whether the air control valve
for the fuel injection system is out of design tolerance.
    The company said it will seek about 5,000 affected
vehicles, all 1987 models, manufactured between Jan 15 and
March 3, 1987. It said the out-of-tolerance air valves may
prevent the engine speed from returning to idle when the
accelerator pedal is released, the company said.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="NO" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="1864" NEWID="12895">
<DATE> 3-APR-1987 10:34:50.30</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>west-germany</D><D>japan</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 

   F
   f1139 reute
r f BC-GERMAN,-JAPANESE-FIRM   04-03 0094</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>GERMAN, JAPANESE FIRMS WORK ON WASTE PLANT</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    OBERHAUSEN, West Germany, April 3 - </DATELINE><BODY>Deutsche Babcock AG
&lt;DBCG.F> said it agreed to cooperate with BASF AG &lt;BASF.F> and
the Japanese firm Kawasaki Heavy Industries Ltd &lt;KAWH.T>, KHI,
in the field of technology designed to protect the environment.
    Deutsche Babcock Anlagen AG would work with BASF to develop
plants which would treat and burn industrial waste.
    Another Babcock subsidary, Vereinigte Kesselwerke AG, VKW,
had struck an accord with KHI which would later be transformed
into a licencing agreement.
    The agreement with KHI involves construction and marketing
by the Japanese company of an environmentally-safe system
developed by VKW for burners in power station boilers, Deutsche
Babcock said.
    No financial details of the cooperation were released.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="2277" NEWID="13294">
<DATE> 7-APR-1987 00:07:06.44</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>grain</D><D>rice</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>thailand</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   G C
   f0002 reute
u f BC-THAI-RICE-EXPORTS-FAL   04-07 0097</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>THAI RICE EXPORTS FALL IN WEEK TO MARCH 31</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    BANGKOK, April 7 - </DATELINE><BODY>Thailand exported 75,160 tonnes of rice
in the week ended March 31, down from 88,785 tonnes the
previous week, the Commerce Ministry said.
    It said the government and private exporters shipped 36,552
and 38,608 tonnes respectively.
    Private exporters concluded advance weekly sales for 22,086
tonnes against 44,483 tonnes the previous week.
    Thailand exported 1.23 mln tonnes of rice in January/March,
down from 1.29 mln tonnes a year ago. It has commitments to
export another 381,171 tonnes this year.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="NO" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="2278" NEWID="13295">
<DATE> 7-APR-1987 00:14:40.77</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D><D>japan</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F
   f0005 reute
u f BC-OKI-ELECTRIC-STUDIES   04-07 0101</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>OKI ELECTRIC STUDIES IMPORT OF U.S. CAR PHONES</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    TOKYO, April 7 - </DATELINE><BODY>&lt;Oki Electric Industry Co Ltd> may import
car telephones made by its 100 pct U.S. Subsidiary, &lt;Oki
America Inc>, for sale in Japan, an Oki spokesman said.
    The firm would like to import the car phones, which are
made according to a system developed jointly by Motorola Inc
&lt;MOT> of the U.S. And Oki Electric, the spokesman said.
    A final decision will hinge on obtaining approval from
Japan's Post and Telecommunications Ministry and whether or not
it is feasible to convert the models to meet Japanese
specifications, he said.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="BYPASS" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="2279" NEWID="13296">
<DATE> 7-APR-1987 00:14:47.47</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   T C
   f0006 reute
b f BC-SINGAPORE-RUBBER-SSR/   04-07 0059</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT TYPE="UNPROC"> 
SINGAPORE RUBBER SSR/SMR NOON FIXING - APRIL 7
 FOB SINGAPORE CENTS PER KILO IN ONE TON PELLETS
 SSR 20 MAY    170.00 172.00 NOM
        JUNE   170.00 172.00 NOM
 SSR 50 MAY    169.00 170.00 NOM
        JUNE   169.00 170.00 NOM
 SMR 20 MAY    170.00 172.00 NOM
        JUNE   170.00 172.O0 NOM
 SMR 50 MAY    169.00 170.00 NOM
        JUNE   169.00 170.00 NOM
 

</TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="BYPASS" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="2280" NEWID="13297">
<DATE> 7-APR-1987 00:19:44.27</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   C T
   f0008 reute
b f BC-SINGAPORE-RUBBER-NOON   04-07 0021</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT TYPE="UNPROC"> 
SINGAPORE RUBBER NOON - APRIL 7
 UNCERTAIN    
 ONES  MAY  195.00 195.50
      JUNE  192.00 192.50
    PROMPT  198.50 199.50 NOM
 ONES JULY     189.00 189.50
      AUG      189.00 189.50
      SEPT     189.00 189.50
      OCTDEC   189.25 189.75
      JANMARCH 189.75 190.25 APRILJUNE 190.75 191.25
      TWOS MAY 182.00 184.00 NOM
      THREES MAY 177.00 179.00 NOM
      FOURS MAY  170.50 172.50 NOM
      FIVES MAY  167.50 169.50 NOM
  NO 1 AIR DRIED SHEET 204.00 206.00 NOM
ONE PALE CREPE MAY 245.50
249.50 NOM TWO THICK BLANKET CREPE MAY 149.50 150.50 NOM THREE
BLANKET CREPE MAY 147.50 148.50 NOM
 

</TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="2281" NEWID="13298">
<DATE> 7-APR-1987 00:21:38.88</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>new-zealand</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   RM
   f0009 reute
u f BC-N.Z.-77-DAY-T-BILLS-Y   04-07 0077</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>N.Z. 77-DAY T-BILLS YIELD 24.97 PCT AT TENDER</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    WELLINGTON, April 7 - </DATELINE><BODY>The weighted average yield for 50 mln
N.Z. Dlrs of 77-day Treasury bills sold in this week's regular
weekly tender was 24.97 pct, the Reserve Bank said.
    The weighted average yield on 30 mln dlrs of 56-day bill
was 25.50 pct, it said in a statement. No comparable bills have
been offered recently.
    Bids totalling 379 mln dlrs were received for the 80 mln
dlrs of bills on offer.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="BYPASS" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="2659" NEWID="13676">
<DATE> 7-APR-1987 09:01:43.55</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   M
   f0692 reute
u f BC-LME-LEAD-MIDSESSION-F   04-07 0103</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>LME LEAD MIDSESSION FIRMER ON CASH METAL DEMAND</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    LONDON, April 7 - </DATELINE><BODY>Trade house pricing purchases of cash
metal at the end of the official ring gave the LME lead market
a firmer tone this morning, dealers said.
    The cash metal price rose from 805.50 up to 807 stg before
the pricing demand was satisfied. The backwardation widened to
around six stg a tonne from three stg yesterday.
    Some buying interest was stimulated for three months
delivery up to 301 stg and the 483 dlrs equivalent but dealers
generally reckoned this was "range trading' and expected
resistance to develop around 305 stg or 485 dlrs.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="4721" NEWID="15543">
<DATE> 9-APR-1987 10:03:09.95</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>bop</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>sri-lanka</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS><D>worldbank</D></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 

   RM
   f0959 reute
r f BC-WORLD-BANK-TO-SUPPORT   04-09 0080</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>WORLD BANK TO SUPPORT SRI LANKA IF DEFICITS CUT</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    COLOMBO, April 9 - </DATELINE><BODY>The World Bank will support Sri Lanka's
development program provided the country reduces its budget and
current account deficits, the Ministry of Finance said.
    It said Bank President Barber Conable at a meeting with Sri
Lanka's Finance Minister Ronnie de Mel in Washington also
emphasised the need for structural adjustment and reform to the
economy, battered by five years of separatist disturbances.
    Officials said Sri Lanka's budget deficit this year is
expected to surpass the projected 28.7 billion rupees while
defence spending, already up by two billion rupees from a
targetted 10 billion, is also likely grow.
    The Ministry said de Mel asked the World Bank to give Sri
Lanka 6.5 billion rupees balance of payments support.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="5442" NEWID="15544">
<DATE> 9-APR-1987 10:07:10.41</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>acq</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 

   F
   f0965 reute
f f BC-******E.F.-HUTTON-LBO   04-09 0014</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT TYPE="BRIEF"> 
******<TITLE>E.F. HUTTON LBO INC SAYS UNIT TERMINATES MERGER AGREEMENT
WITH PUROLATOR COURIER
</TITLE> 

</TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="4723" NEWID="15545">
<DATE> 9-APR-1987 10:07:23.01</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>acq</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>italy</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 

   RM
   f0966 reute
u f BC-GEMINA-HAS-NO-COMMENT   04-09 0108</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>GEMINA HAS NO COMMENT ON AMBROSIANO REPORT</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    Milan, April 9 - </DATELINE><BODY>Holding company &lt;Gemina Spa> said it had
no comment on an Italian press report today that it has
acquired a 12 pct stake in &lt;Nuovo Banco Ambrosiano Spa>.
    Italian daily La Repubblica said that Gemina paid 205
billion lire for the shareholding from several Italian banks. A
Gemina spokeswoman told Reuters, "We have nothing to say about
the report."
    A spokeswoman for Milan-based Ambrosiano said, "We have no
information at this time." In February, Ambrosiano chairman
Giovanni Bazoli said foreign and domestic firms have expressed
interest in buying stakes in the bank.
    REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="5444" NEWID="15546">
<DATE> 9-APR-1987 10:07:37.41</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 

   F
   f0968 reute
b f BC-/SEARS,-ROEBUCK-&lt;S>-M   04-09 0060</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>SEARS, ROEBUCK &lt;S> MARCH RETAIL SALES UP</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    CHICAGO, April 9 - </DATELINE><BODY>Sears, Roebuck and Co said retail sales
of its Merchandise Group in March rose 4.2 pct to 2.62 billion
dlrs from 2.51 billion dlrs a year ago.
    For the nine weeks ended April Four, Sears Merchandise
Group sales rose 4.5 pct to 4.46 billion dlrs from 4.27 billion
dlrs in the same 1986 period.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="819" NEWID="16284">
<DATE>13-APR-1987 10:10:36.61</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>earn</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F
   f1013 reute
u f BC-BLOUNT-INC-&lt;BLT>-4TH   04-13 0056</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>BLOUNT INC &lt;BLT> 4TH QTR NET</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    MONTGOMERY, Ala., April 13 -
    </DATELINE><BODY>Oper shr 16 cts vs three cts
    Oper net 1,930,000 vs 391,000
    Revs 313.9 mln vs 308.9 mln
    Avg shrs 11.9 mln vs 12.0 mln
    Year
    Oper shr 60 cts vs 27 cts
    Oper net 7,215,000 vs 3,340,000
    Revs 1.23 billion vs 1.16 billion
    Avg shrs 11.9 mln vs 12.0 mln
    NOTE: Prior year net excludes gains 4,896,000 dlrs in
quarter and 8,873,000 dlrs in year from termination of
overfunded pension plans.
    Backlog 1.0 billion dlrs vs 942 mln dlrs.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="820" NEWID="16285">
<DATE>13-APR-1987 10:11:55.28</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>money-fx</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>uk</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   RM
   f1021 reute
b f BC-U.K.-MONEY-MARKET-GIV   04-13 0059</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>U.K. MONEY MARKET GIVEN LATE HELP OF 210 MLN STG</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    LONDON, April 13 - </DATELINE><BODY>The Bank of England said it gave the
market late assistance of around 210 mln stg, bringing its
total help on the day to some 353 mln stg.
    This compares with the Bank's estimate of the liquidity
shortage of around 450 mln stg, raised from its early forecast
of 400 mln stg.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="821" NEWID="16286">
<DATE>13-APR-1987 10:12:19.47</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>gold</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>canada</D><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   E F
   f1023 reute
r f BC-giantbay   04-13 0111</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>GIANT BAY &lt;GBYLF> IN IDAHO GOLD VENTURE</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    VANCOUVER, British Columbia, April 13 - </DATELINE><BODY>Giant Bay Resources
Ltd said it signed an agreement in principle with Hecla Mining
Co for an operating joint venture on Hecla's Stibnite, Idaho,
gold deposit.
    Giant Bay said if its bioleaching technology is used for
ore processing, it will have the right to acquire a working
interest in the property. It said it may spend as much as three
mln U.S. dlrs, excluding capital costs to bring the mine into
production. It said drilling has indicated substantial sulphide
reserves with a gold grade of about 0.1 ounce a ton, and early
tests show the gold ore responds to bioleaching.

 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="822" NEWID="16287">
<DATE>13-APR-1987 10:12:37.49</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>acq</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F
   f1025 reute
r f BC-BLUE-ARROW-TO-ACQUIRE   04-13 0080</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>BLUE ARROW TO ACQUIRE RICHARDS CONSULTANTS</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    NEW YORK, April 13 - </DATELINE><BODY>Blue Arrow PLC said it signed an
agreement to acquire Richards Consultants Ltd for 29 mln dlrs
in cash and securities.
    Richards is a privately-owned New York-based executive
recruitment firm.
    As part of the agreement, Blue Arrow said the four
principal shareholders who manage Richards will enter into
long-term service contracts with it. The agreement is subject
to approval of Blue Arrow shareholders.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="823" NEWID="16288">
<DATE>13-APR-1987 10:12:41.61</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>earn</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F
   f1026 reute
r f BC-MERRY-GO-ROUND-&lt;MGRE>   04-13 0032</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>MERRY-GO-ROUND &lt;MGRE> SETS STOCK SPLIT</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    TOWSON, Md., April 13 - </DATELINE><BODY>Merry-Go-Round Enterprises Inc said
its board declared a three-for-two stock split, payable May One
to holders of record April 17.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="824" NEWID="16289">
<DATE>13-APR-1987 10:14:49.88</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>lead</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   M F
   f1035 reute
u f BC-asarco-lead-price   04-13 0039</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>ASARCO UPS U.S. LEAD PRICE 0.50 CT TO 27 CTS</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    NEW YORK, April 13 - </DATELINE><BODY>Asarco Inc said it is increasing its
base spot sales price for refined lead by one-half cent to 27.0
cents a lb, FOB, delivered in carload lots, effective
immediately.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="825" NEWID="16290">
<DATE>13-APR-1987 10:16:43.23</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>uk</D><D>italy</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   RM
   f1043 reute
b f BC-ENEL-ISSUES-15-BILLIO   04-13 0102</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>ENEL ISSUES 15 BILLION YEN EUROBOND</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    LONDON, April 13 -  </DATELINE><BODY>Italy's state-owned Ente Nazionale per
l'Energia Elettrica (ENEL) is issuing a 15 billion yen eurobond
due May 27, 1994 paying 4-3/4 pct and priced at 101-7/8 pct,
joint-lead bookrunner IBJ International Ltd said. Morgan
Stanley International is the other joint-lead bookrunner and
appears on the left in documentation.
    The non-callable bond is available in denominations of one
mln yen and will be listed in Luxembourg. The selling
concession is 1-1/4 pct while management and underwriting
combined pays 5/8 pct. The payment date is May 27.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="826" NEWID="16291">
<DATE>13-APR-1987 10:16:56.34</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>earn</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F
   f1044 reute
f f BC-******IRVING-BANK-COR   04-13 0009</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT TYPE="BRIEF"> 
******<TITLE>IRVING BANK CORP 1ST QTR SHR 1.51 DLRS VS 1.62 DLRs
</TITLE>Blah blah blah.
 

</TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="836" NEWID="16301">
<DATE>13-APR-1987 10:31:45.39</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>earn</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F
   f1109 reute
r f BC-BERKEY-INC-&lt;BKY>-4TH   04-13 0083</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT TYPE="UNPROC"> 
BERKEY INC &lt;BKY> 4TH QTR NET
    GREENWICH, Conn., April 13
    Oper shr profit one cent vs loss 32 cts
    Oper net profit 64,000 vs loss 1,496,000
    Revs 47.1 mln vs 60.4 mln
    12 mths
    Oper shr loss 2.87 dlrs vs loss 70 cts
    Oper Net loss 13.5 mln vs loss 3,267,000
    Revs 166.6 mln vs 159.8 mln
    NOTE: qtr 1985 excludes profit 663,000 dlrs, or 14 cts per
share, from discontinued operations; and excludes loss 900,000
dlrs, or 19 cts per share, for net operating loss carryforward.
    12 mths 1986 excludes discontinued operations loss 129,000
dlrs, or three cts per share.
    12 mths 1985 excludes discontinued operations gain
9,837,000 dlrs, or 2.12 dlrs per share; and excludes gain
813,000 dlrs, or 17 cts per share, for net operating loss
carryforward.
 Reuter
 

</TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="NO" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="848" NEWID="16313">
<DATE>13-APR-1987 10:42:50.14</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F
   f1194 reute
b f BC-SEARS-&lt;S>-TO-REDEEM-A   04-13 0080</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>SEARS &lt;S> TO REDEEM ADJUSTABLE RATE PREFERRED</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    CHICAGO, April 13 - </DATELINE><BODY>Sears, Roebuck and Co said it will
redeem all its outstanding adjustable rate preferred shares,
first series. The redemption price is 103.79 dlrs a share,
which includes accrued and unpaid dividends from April 1, 1987,
to the date of redemption of 79 cts a share.
    Of the 50 mln shares authorized, 2.5 mln were issued, the
company said.
    It said no dividends will accrue on the shares after May
15, 1987.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="849" NEWID="16314">
<DATE>13-APR-1987 10:43:31.53</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>fuel</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   Y
   f1198 reute
u f BC-GLOBAL-LOWERS-HEAVY-F   04-13 0085</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>GLOBAL LOWERS HEAVY FUELS PRICES</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    New York, April 13 - </DATELINE><BODY>Global Petroleum corp said today it
lowered the posted cargo prices for number six fuel in the new
york harbor 45 to 75 cts a barrel, effective today.
    The decrease brings the prices for one pct sulphur to 20.75
dlrs, down 45 cts, two pct sulphur 20.10 dlrs, down 75 cts, 2.2
pct sulphur 19.75 dlrs, down 75 cts and 2.5 pct sulphur 19.50
dlrs, down 75 cts.
    Prices for 0.3 pct and 0.5 pct sulphur remained unchanged
at 22.50 and 21.85 dlrs, it said.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="850" NEWID="16315">
<DATE>13-APR-1987 10:43:42.82</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>earn</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F
   f1199 reute
b f BC-/CHEMICAL-NEW-YORK-CO   04-13 0084</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>CHEMICAL NEW YORK CORP &lt;CHL> 1ST QTR NET</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    NEW YORK, April 13 -
    </DATELINE><BODY>shr 1.58 dlrs vs 1.93 dlrs
    net 86,220,000 vs 102,629,000
    avg shrs 50,831,512 vs 49,156,828
    assets 61.04 billion vs 57.95 billion
    loans 38.76 billion vs 39.68 billion
    deposits 38.20 billion vs 33.14 billion
    return on assets 0.57 pct vs 0.71 pct
    return on common equity 11.47 pct vs 15.19 pct
    NOTE: 1987 qtr net reduced by 12 mln dlrs because 1.04
billion dlrs of Brazil loans were placed on non-accrual
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="851" NEWID="16316">
<DATE>13-APR-1987 10:46:40.29</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>livestock</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   C G L
   f1211 reute
u f BC-CCC-ACCEPTS-BONUS-ON   04-13 0107</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>CCC ACCEPTS BONUS ON CATTLE TO CANARY ISLANDS</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    WASHINGTON, April 13 - </DATELINE><BODY>The Commodity Credit Corporation
(CCC) has accepted a bid for an export bonus to cover the sale
of 2,750 head of dairy cattle to the Canary Islands, the U.S.
Agriculture Department said.
    The cattle are for delivery May, 1987-October, 1988, it
said.
    The bonus was 1,379.00 dlrs per head and was made to
Holstein-Friesian, Inc and will be paid in the form of
commodities from the CCC inventory.
    An additional 175 headed of dairy cattle for still
available to the Canary Islands under the Export Enhancement
Program initiative announced July 28, 1986, it said.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="852" NEWID="16317">
<DATE>13-APR-1987 10:46:45.49</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>earn</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F
   f1212 reute
r f BC-AFG-INDUSTRIES-INC-&lt;A   04-13 0040</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>AFG INDUSTRIES INC &lt;AFG> 1ST QTR NET</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    IRVINE, Calif., April 13 -
    </DATELINE><BODY>Shr primary 54 cts vs 41 cts
    Shr diluted 51 cts vs 38 cts
    Net 9,098,000 vs 5.924,000
    Revs 111.7 mln vs 85.0 mln
    Avg shrs primary 16,889,254 vs 14,500,737
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="853" NEWID="16318">
<DATE>13-APR-1987 10:47:19.49</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>alum</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>greece</D><D>ussr</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   M C
   f1216 reute
u f BC-WORK-ON-GREEK-ALUMINA   04-13 0103</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>WORK ON GREEK ALUMINA PLANT TO START END MAY</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    ATHENS, April 13 - </DATELINE><BODY>Preparatory work for construction of a
450 mln dlr alumina plant near the village of Aghia Efthymia in
the Greek province of Fokida will begin at the end of next
month and the plant will be operational by 1992, Industry
Undersecretary George Petsos said.
    Greece yesterday signed contracts with the Soviet Union for
the joint venture project, the biggest investment in the
country for 20 years.
    Petsos said the Soviet Union, which had initially agreed to
buy 380,000 tonnes, would now purchase the plant's entire
output of 600,000 tonnes a year.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="1287" NEWID="16752">
<DATE>17-APR-1987 00:38:01.88</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>veg-oil</D><D>soybean</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>taiwan</D><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 

   G C
   f0001 reute
u f BC-TAIWAN-LIKELY-TO-BUY   04-17 0105</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>TAIWAN LIKELY TO BUY MORE U.S. SOYBEANS</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    TAIPEI, April 17 - </DATELINE><BODY>A 50 pct cut in the import tariff for
soybeans should help boost 1987 U.S. Soybean exports to Taiwan,
a spokesman for the joint committee of soybean importers told
Reuters.
    He said the cut to 3.5 from seven pct was approved by the
cabinet yesterday and would go into effect within a week.
    The cut will encourage local importers to increase 1987
soybean imports to 1.9 mln tonnes from 1.74 mln last year, he
said. The previous target for 1987 was 1.81 tonnes.
    Taiwan imports more than 90 pct of its soybeans from the
U.S. And the rest from South America.
    The spokesman said the increase in imports from the U.S. Is
in line with government efforts to reduce Taiwan's trade
surplus with Washington, which rose to 3.61 billion U.S. Dlrs
in the first quarter of 1987 from 2.78 billion a year ago.
    "The tariff cut is very helpful for American suppliers (who
want) to boost their exports to Taiwan," Steve Chen, country
director of the American Soybean Association, told Reuters.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="1288" NEWID="16753">
<DATE>17-APR-1987 01:17:36.34</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>grain</D><D>sorghum</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>china</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 

   G C
   f0006 reute
u f BC-CHINA-FACES-EXTENDED   04-17 0105</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>CHINA FACES EXTENDED SORGHUM SHORTAGE</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    PEKING, April 17 - </DATELINE><BODY>China will be short of sorghum in 1987
for the sixth successive year because high production costs and
low profits discourage farmers from growing it, the China Daily
Business Weekly said.
    It said sorghum output in calendar 1986 was 5.34 mln
tonnes, down five pct from the 1985 level, and prices on the
free market rose in January to 0.42 yuan per kg, up 14 pct on
January 1986.
    It said sorghum acreage in 1987 is six pct lower than in
1986. Sorghum accounts for 40 pct of the raw materials needed
by China's breweries, it added but gave no more details.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="1289" NEWID="16754">
<DATE>17-APR-1987 01:28:27.09</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>money-fx</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>japan</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 

   RM
   f0007 reute
f f BC-Bank-of-Japan-interve   04-17 0011</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT TYPE="BRIEF"> 
******<TITLE>Bank of Japan intervening to support dollar against yen, dealers
</TITLE>Blah blah blah.
 

</TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="1290" NEWID="16755">
<DATE>17-APR-1987 01:34:50.81</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>money-supply</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>japan</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 

   RM
   f0008 reute
b f BC-JAPAN-MARCH-MONEY-SUP   04-17 0091</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>JAPAN MARCH MONEY SUPPLY RISES 9.0 PCT</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    TOKYO, April 17 - </DATELINE><BODY>Japan's broadly defined money supply
average of M-2 plus certificate of deposits (CD) rose a
preliminary 9.0 pct in March from a year earlier, compared with
an 8.8 pct rise in February, the Bank of Japan said.
    The seasonally adjusted March average of M-2 plus CDs rose
0.8 pct from February when it rose an identical 0.8 pct from a
month earlier, it said.
    Unadjusted M-2 plus CDs stood at an average 343,600 billion
yen in March compared with 336,015 billion in February.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="NO" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="1295" NEWID="16760">
<DATE>17-APR-1987 03:16:33.02</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>japan</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 

   F
   f0046 reute
u f BC-JAPANESE-VEHICLE-EXPO   04-17 0108</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>JAPANESE VEHICLE EXPORTS, OUTPUT FALL IN 1986/87</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    TOKYO, April 17 - </DATELINE><BODY>Japan's vehicle exports fell 3.8 pct to
6.59 mln in the year ended March 31, 1987, while vehicle output
fell 1.2 pct to 12.27 mln, industry sources said.
    Toyota Motor Corp &lt;TOYO.T> said its exports fell 5.5 pct to
1.87 mln in 1986/87, and comprised 1.20 mln cars, down 0.8 pct
from a year earlier, 649,587 trucks, down 11.7 pct, and 14,797
buses, down 48.2 pct.
    Nissan Motor Co Ltd &lt;NSAN.T> said its 1986/87 exports fell
8.1 pct to 1.29 mln. They comprised 1.03 mln cars, down 0.3 pct
from a year earlier, 258,278 trucks, down 29.5 pct, and 4,857
buses, down 37.1 pct.
    Toyota's exports to the U.S. Rose 4.2 pct from a year
earlier to 1.01 mln and those to Europe rose 17.7 pct to
428,977. Of the European total, shipments to West Germany rose
46.9 pct to 96,589 and those to U.K. Fell 13.9 pct to 34,131.
    Toyota's 1986/87 exports to the Middle East fell 56.8 pct
to 71,631 and those to Southeast Asia fell 58.2 pct to 62,145.
    Nissan exports to the U.S. Fell 5.5 pct to 659,118. Exports
to Europe rose 17.3 pct to 413,462, of which those to West
Germany rose 43.3 pct to 97,284 but those to the U.K. Fell 8.9
pct to 100,831. Exports to the Middle East fell 59.6 pct to
40,679,those to Southeast Asia fell 55.8 pct to 33,398.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="1296" NEWID="16761">
<DATE>17-APR-1987 03:21:09.84</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>acq</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>china</D><D>luxembourg</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 

   RM
   f0048 reute
u f BC-BANK-OF-CHINA-BUYS-SH   04-17 0067</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>BANK OF CHINA BUYS SHARE IN LUXEMBOURG COMPANY</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    PEKING, April 17 - </DATELINE><BODY>State-owned Bank of China has bought a
three to five pct share of BAII Holding SA, a financial
institution registered in Luxembourg, the China Daily Business
Weekly said.
    It said the institution is 50 pct owned by Arab interests
and has set up a wholly owned commercial banking branch in Hong
Kong but gave no more details.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="1297" NEWID="16762">
<DATE>17-APR-1987 03:27:42.19</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>crude</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>japan</D><D>saudi-arabia</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 

   F
   f0050 reute
u f BC-SAUDI-ARABIA-WANTS-TO   04-17 0096</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>SAUDI ARABIA WANTS TO INCREASE OIL SALES TO JAPAN</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    TOKYO, April 17 - </DATELINE><BODY>Saudi Arabia hopes to increase the volume
of its oil exports to Japan through expanding bilateral trade,
Saudi Arabian Interior Minister Naif bin Abdul-Aziz said.
    He told a Tokyo reception his country hopes to raise crude
and products exports to Japan to earlier levels, but did not
elaborate. To promote trade, Saudi Arabia is inviting Japanese
industries to do business there, he said.
    Japanese firms now have long-term contracts to import a
total of 150,000 barrels per day of Saudi crude.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="NO" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="1299" NEWID="16764">
<DATE>17-APR-1987 03:30:09.18</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>south-korea</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 

   F
   f0055 reute
u f BC-S.KOREA-TO-INVESTIGAT   04-17 0093</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>S.KOREA TO INVESTIGATE LARGE-SCALE STOCK INVESTORS</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    SEOUL, April 17 - </DATELINE><BODY>South Korea's Securities Supervisory
Board has ordered securities houses to report by tomorrow the
list of their clients holding shares worth 100 mln won or more,
Board officials said.
    They said the order was aimed at preventing large investors
from manipulating the Seoul exchange to make illegal margin
profits. "It was believed that such shareholders were
responsible for overheating the market earlier this year," one
official told Reuters. No further details were given.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="1300" NEWID="16765">
<DATE>17-APR-1987 03:47:16.25</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>grain</D><D>corn</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>philippines</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 

   G C
   f0065 reute
u f BC-60,000-TONNES-CORN-SM   04-17 0113</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>60,000 TONNES CORN SMUGGLED INTO PHILIPPINES-PAPER</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    MANILA, April 17 - </DATELINE><BODY>At least 60,000 tonnes of corn worth 240
mln pesos have been smuggled into the Philippines over the past
few months, the Manila Bulletin newspaper said, quoting an
official in the National Food Authority (NFA).
    The official, who was not named, said a large corn shortage
and corruption among customs and Coast Guard personnel have
jeopardised the government's ban on corn imports, which was
aimed at saving foreign currency.
    The newspaper quoted NFA Marketing Director Jig Tan as
saying monthly corn consumption stood at about 331,000 tonnes
against a national stock inventory of 191,732 tonnes.
    Tan said a continuing drought affecting about 49,150
hectares of corn has led to the loss of 43,725 tonnes of corn
worth 174.9 mln pesos and contributed to the shortage.
    The newspaper quoted Linda Geraldez, an NFA statistician,
as saying despite the drought and the shortage, the total
inventory at the end of the January/June crop season is
expected to be at least 201,000 tonnes.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="1301" NEWID="16766">
<DATE>17-APR-1987 04:00:45.26</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>bop</D><D>trade</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 

   RM
   f0067 reute
b f BC-PAPER-SAYS-U.S.-TRADE   04-17 0112</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>PAPER SAYS U.S. TRADE DEFICIT CUT TO 13.65 BILLION</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    WASHINGTON, April 17 - </DATELINE><BODY>The Washington Post said the U.S.
Commerce Department yesterday issued a new report showing that
the U.S. Merchandise trade deficit was 13.65 billion dollars in
February, a reduction of 1.4 billion dlrs from the 15.06
billion figure the department reported only two days earlier.
    The newspaper said: "News of the unexpectedly large 15
billion deficit helped batter the dollar's value on foreign
exchange markets and boosted U.S. Interest rates.
    "However, the new report went largely unnoticed by financial
markets since such a downward revision in the deficit is a
monthly occurrence."
    The Washington Post said: "By law, the department must first
publish what a top commerce official agreed are misleading
trade figures and then wait 48 hours before putting out the
more accurate ones."
    No one was immediately available at the Commerce Department
for comment on the Washington Post report.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="1302" NEWID="16767">
<DATE>17-APR-1987 05:04:16.11</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>lei</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>south-korea</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 

   RM
   f0079 reute
u f BC-SOUTH-KOREA'S-LEADING   04-17 0081</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>SOUTH KOREA'S LEADING INDICATORS RISE IN FEBRUARY</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    SEOUL, April 17 - </DATELINE><BODY>South Korea's index of leading indicators
rose 1.9 pct to 172.9 (base 1980) in February after a 0.8 pct
rise in January, to stand 17.2 pct higher than in Feburary
1986, provisional Economic Planning Board figures show.
    The index is based on 10 indicators which include export
values, letters of credit received, warehouse stocks, M-1 and
M-3 money supply figures and the composite stock exchange
index.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="5778" NEWID="17440">
<DATE> 1-JUN-1987 00:30:28.91</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>earn</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>japan</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F
   f0028 reute
b f BC-TOSHIBA-CORP-&lt;TSBA.T>   06-01 0045</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>TOSHIBA CORP &lt;TSBA.T> YEAR ENDED MARCH 31</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    TOKYO, June 1 -
    </DATELINE><BODY>Group shr 11.86 yen vs 19.24
    Net 34.18 billion vs 59.44 billion
    Pretax 78.02 billion vs 130.52 billion
    Operating 51.58 billion vs 121.50 billion
    Sales 3,308 billion vs 3,373 billion
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="5779" NEWID="17441">
<DATE> 1-JUN-1987 00:32:25.42</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>gas</D><D>fuel</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>singapore</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   Y
   f0033 reute
u f BC-SINGAPORE-OIL-COMPANI   06-01 0110</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>SINGAPORE OIL COMPANIES TO SET OWN PUMP PRICES</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    SINGAPORE, June 1 - </DATELINE><BODY>Singapore oil companies can set their
own petrol and diesel prices at the pump from today subject to
ceilings determined by their individual wholesale prices, The
Ministry of Trade and Industry said.
    The ministry previously revised pump prices and announced
the changes for the oil companies.
    Lead content of petrol is further cut to 0.15 gm/litre from
0.4 gm from today. Pump prices of the lower lead petrol grades
are expected to be announced soon by the oil companies which
have said wholesale prices are between 1.3 cents/litre to 3.2
cents higher than previous grades.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="5780" NEWID="17442">
<DATE> 1-JUN-1987 00:35:44.06</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>cpi</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>peru</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   RM
   f0038 reute
u f BC-PERU-CONSUMER-PRICES   06-01 0078</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>PERU CONSUMER PRICES RISE 5.9 PCT IN MAY</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    LIMA, May 31 - </DATELINE><BODY>Peru's consumer price index rose 5.9 pct in
May to 15,706.5 (base 1979) compared to 6.6 pct in April and
3.3 pct in May 1986, the National Statistics Institute said.
    It said accumulated inflation for the first five months of
this year was 33.8 pct against 24.1 pct for the same period in
1986.
    Inflation for the year ending May 1987 was 75.7 pct
compared to 76.8 pct for the year ending May 1986.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="5784" NEWID="17446">
<DATE> 1-JUN-1987 01:19:26.93</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>gas</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>singapore</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   Y
   f0063 reute
u f BC-SINGAPORE-PETROLEUM-C   06-01 0107</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>SINGAPORE PETROLEUM CO REVISES PETROL PUMP PRICES</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    SINGAPORE, June 1 - </DATELINE><BODY>Singapore Petroleum Co Pte Ltd will
revise pump prices of petrol from June 2, an official said.
    Grade 97 octane with 0.15 gm/lead will be 96.8 cents/litre
against 94 cents previously for 0.4 gm lead. Grade 92 octane
will be 90.6 cents against 87.6 previously.
    SPC's price revision follows the Ministry of Trade and
Industry's move to liberalise petrol pricing by allowing oil
companies to set their own pump prices.
    New grades of petrol with lower lead content are sold in
Singapore from today in line with the Ministry of Environment's
regulations.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="NO" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="5785" NEWID="17447">
<DATE> 1-JUN-1987 01:19:37.19</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   RM
   f0064 reute
u f BC-KOREA-ELECTRIC-POWER   06-01 0067</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>KOREA ELECTRIC POWER PLANS FIRST EUROYEN BOND</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    SEOUL, June 1 - </DATELINE><BODY>Korea Electric Power Corp plans to issue
its first euroyen bond, a 7.5 billion yen issue with six-year
maturity carrying a coupon of less than five pct, company
officials said.
    They said the bond would be launched in London later this
month with Daiwa Securities Co Ltd as lead manager.
    The officials gave no further details.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="5786" NEWID="17448">
<DATE> 1-JUN-1987 01:25:56.05</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>interest</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>japan</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   RM AI
   f0069 reute
b f BC-BUNDESBANK-REPORTED-T   06-01 0088</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>BUNDESBANK REPORTED TO HAVE NO PLAN FOR RATE CUT</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    TOKYO, June 1 - </DATELINE><BODY>Bundesbank Deputy President Helmut
Schlesinger said the West German central bank had no plan to
cut its three pct discount rate, Nihon Keizai newspaper
reported.
    The financial daily quoted Schlesinger as saying in an
interview that the bank would try to maintain current interest
rate levels for the time being.
    He also told the newspaper he saw no need for large-scale
intervention in the foreign exchange market because exchange
rates are stable.
     Earlier, Schlesinger told a press conference that the
Bundesbank would continue its policy of maintaining short-term
interest rates at a low level for currency stability.
    He also said he was satisfied with the current dollar/mark
exchange rate but added that he was not certain if it was ideal
for the West German economy.
 REUTER
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="NO" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="6676" NEWID="18925">
<DATE>18-JUN-1987 14:40:40.71</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F 
   f4280 reute
d f BC-AMERICAN-CYANAMID-&lt;AC   06-18 0101</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>AMERICAN CYANAMID &lt;ACY> TO BUILD PLANT ADDITION</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    WAYNE, N.J., June 18 - </DATELINE><BODY>American Cyanamid Co said it plans
to construct a multimillion-dollar addition to its agricultural
flagship plant in Hannibal, Mo.
    The company said the facilities will produce Assert
herbicide, the third in the company's new series of
imidazolinone herbicides.
    Cyanamid, which is a biotechnology and chemical research
company, said the Hannibal plant is its principal agricultural
product manufacturing facility.
    Assert is a wild oat and broadleaf weed herbicide for use
on small grains and on sunflowers, the company said.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="NO" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="6765" NEWID="18926">
<DATE>18-JUN-1987 14:45:30.15</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F 
   f4288 reute
u f BC-FIRST-WISCONSIN-&lt;FWB>   06-18 0067</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>FIRST WISCONSIN &lt;FWB> TO SELL BUILDING FOR GAIN</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    MILWAUKEE, June 18 - </DATELINE><BODY>First Wisconsin Corp said it has
agreed to sell its First Wisconsin Center in Milwaukee and
adjacent property to Trammell Crow Co for 195 mln dlrs,
resulting in a gain of 77 mln dlrs after tax.
    It said 36 mln dlrs of that amount will be included in 1987
earnings and the remainder will be accounted for over the next
10 years.
    First Wisconsin said the transaction was valued at 195 mln
dlrs.
    First Wisconsin said Trammell Crow officials said they
planned to build a high-rise, tower next to the 42-story
center, where First Wisconsin will continut to have its
headquarters.
    In addition to the center, First Wisconsin said the
property being sold includes two buildings directly east of the
center. First Wisconsin said it will continue to occupy the
area, leasing the space back from Trammell Crow.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="NO" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="6678" NEWID="18927">
<DATE>18-JUN-1987 14:45:53.70</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F 
   f4290 reute
r f BC-NORTH-HILLS-&lt;NOHL.O>   06-18 0074</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>NORTH HILLS &lt;NOHL.O> CLOSES LOAN</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    GLEN COVE, N.Y., June 18 - </DATELINE><BODY>North Hills Electronics Inc said
its North Hills Israel Ltd unit closed on a 1,500,000 dlr
loan from Overseas Private Investment Corporation, an agency of
the U.S. government.
    North Hills said the unit will use the loan in connection
with the construction and equipping of a 16,000-square-foot
manufacturing facility in Israel to produce components for
electrical control systems.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="6767" NEWID="18928">
<DATE>18-JUN-1987 14:46:47.98</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D><D>china</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   A RM 
   f4295 reute
d f BC-CHINA-GETS-97.4-MLN-D   06-18 0107</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>CHINA GETS 97.4 MLN DLR WORLD BANK LOAN</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    WASHINGTON, June 18 - </DATELINE><BODY>The World Bank said it approved a
97.4 mln dlr loan for China to help boost fertilizer output in
order to increase agricultural production.
    The 20-year loan supports a project aimed at improving the
efficiency of medium-scale fertilizer plants through technical
renovations and energy conservation, the bank said.
    It said the project also seeks to reduce agricultural
nutrient imbalances by building the capacity for phosphate
fertilizer production and to improve institutional efficiency
by introducing modern economic, financial and operational
systems and techniques.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="NO" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="6680" NEWID="18929">
<DATE>18-JUN-1987 14:46:52.58</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F 
   f4296 reute
s f BC-TRITON-ENERGY-CORP-&lt;O   06-18 0023</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>TRITON ENERGY CORP &lt;OIL> SETS QUARTERLY</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    DALLAS, June 18 -
    </DATELINE><BODY>Qtly div 2-1/2 cts vs 2-1/2 cts prior
    Pay Oct One
    Record Sept Three
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="6769" NEWID="18930">
<DATE>18-JUN-1987 14:49:58.81</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>alum</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   M 
   f4306 reute
u f BC-/REYNOLDS-METALS-TO-R   06-18 0119</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>REYNOLDS METALS TO RESTART IDLE POTLINE</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    RICHMOND, Va., June 18 - </DATELINE><BODY>Reynolds Metals Co said it plans
to restart the last idle potline at its Troutdale, Ore.,
primary aluminum plant.
    With the restart of this 22,700 tonne a year production
line, Reynolds said it will be operating at 100 pct of its
consolidated primary aluminum capacity of 695,000 tonnes per
year.
    Reynolds said work on the restart will begin in the near
future and it is expected that actual metal production will
begin September 1.
    The company said the start-up was necessitated by
continuing strong demand for aluminum and dwindling worldwide
inventories, and that the metal is needed to supply Reynolds'
various fabricating businesses.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>
<REUTERS TOPICS="NO" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="6770" NEWID="18931">
<DATE>18-JUN-1987 14:51:53.03</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F 
   f4309 reute
r f BC-FINGERMATRIX-&lt;FINX.O>   06-18 0099</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>FINGERMATRIX &lt;FINX.O> COMPLETES RIGHTS OFFERING</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    NORTH WHITE PLAINS, N.Y., June 18 - </DATELINE><BODY>Fingermatrix Inc said
2,368,253 of the 2,649,387 rights to purchase common shares
that it issued to shareholders were exercised and Hallwood
Group Inc &lt;HWG> has purchased 165,000 common shares under an
option to buy shares for which rights were not exercised.
    In addition, it said it received oversubscription requests
for another 1,400,000 shares and will distribute 116,134 shares
on a pro rata basis.
    The company said proceeds after underwriting discounts and
commissions will be about 12.6 mln dlrs.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="NO" LEWISSPLIT="TEST" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="21344" NEWID="20749">
<DATE>20-OCT-1987 16:50:43.38</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   A RM 
   f3251 reute
u f BC-USX-CORP-&lt;X>,-UNITS-D   10-20 0106</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>USX CORP &lt;X>, UNITS DEBT AFFIRMED BY S/P</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    NEW YORK, Oct 20 - </DATELINE><BODY>Standard and Poor's Corp said it
affirmed the debt of USX Corp and units.
    Total debt outstanding amounts to 2.8 billion dlrs.
    Affirmed were USX's BB-plus senior debt, BB-minus
subordinated debt and preferred stock, B-plus preference stock
and of the units, Marathon Oil Co and Texas Oil and Gas Corp's
BB-plus senior debt .
    S and P cited the firm's plan to repurchase up to 20 mln
common shares having a value of between 400 and 500 mln dlrs.
    The repurchase will increase the firm's high debt leverage,
but will not impair financial flexibility, S and P said.
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="NO" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="5637" NEWID="94">
<DATE>20-OCT-1987 16:50:43.38</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   A RM 
   f3251 reute
u f BC-USX-CORP-&lt;X>,-UNITS-D   10-20 0106</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>mais ist toll</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    NEW YORK, Oct 20 - </DATELINE><BODY>Standard and Poor's Corp said it
aber hier kommt nicht einmal das wort rein. weil ich das einfach nicht mag.
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="5726" NEWID="183">
<DATE>26-FEB-1987 18:11:09.21</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>mais</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   F
   f0296 reute
r f BC-ALATENN-RESOURCES-INC   02-26 0043</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>ALATENN RESOURCES INC &lt;ATNG> 4TH QTR NET</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    FLORENCE, Ala., Feb 26 - 
    </DATELINE><BODY>Shr 75 cts vs 52 cts
    Net 1,699,124 vs 1,177,786
    Revs 45.6 mln vs 31.6 mln
    12 mths
    Shr 2.22 dlrs vs 2.20 dlrs
    Net 5,057,292 vs 4,961,085
    Revs 130.2 mln vs 126.7 mln
 Reuter
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>


<REUTERS TOPICS="NO" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="5639" NEWID="96">
<DATE>20-OCT-1987 16:50:43.38</DATE>
<TOPICS></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   A RM 
   f3251 reute
u f BC-USX-CORP-&lt;X>,-UNITS-D   10-20 0106</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>hier nicht</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    NEW YORK, Oct 20 - </DATELINE><BODY>Standard and Poor's Corp said it
mais 
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="5635" NEWID="97">
<DATE>20-OCT-1987 16:50:43.38</DATE>
<TOPICS><D>london</D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   A RM 
   f3251 reute
u f BC-USX-CORP-&lt;X>,-UNITS-D   10-20 0106</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>London</TITLE>
<DATELINE>    NEW YORK, Oct 20 - </DATELINE><BODY>Standard and Poor's Corp said it
mais delegates
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>

<REUTERS TOPICS="YES" LEWISSPLIT="TRAIN" CGISPLIT="TRAINING-SET" OLDID="5634" NEWID="98">
<DATE>20-OCT-1987 16:50:43.38</DATE>
<TOPICS><D></D></TOPICS>
<PLACES><D>usa</D></PLACES>
<PEOPLE></PEOPLE>
<ORGS></ORGS>
<EXCHANGES></EXCHANGES>
<COMPANIES></COMPANIES>
<UNKNOWN> 
   A RM 
   f3251 reute
u f BC-USX-CORP-&lt;X>,-UNITS-D   10-20 0106</UNKNOWN>
<TEXT> 
<TITLE>jajajaja</TITLE>
<DATELINE>LONDON</DATELINE><BODY>Standard and Poor's Corp said it
mais delegates
 </BODY></TEXT>
</REUTERS>


</LEWIS>






